Previously
Are we not having breakfast today? Maid Maria is taking care of it.
Did someone pay? Nothing, boss.
Disaster. It would be.
If it weren't for the order to Montenegro.
They lifted him in the air. Witness's safety,
was your responsibility. Yours were the shippers.
He wants to transport the goods to Italy.
I told him: "Don't do anything stupid, don't mess with Dardan."
If you mention that name again, I'll kill you, got it?
Berisha controls 30% of the heroin trade.
He is linked to extortion, human trafficking, and murder.
Furthermore, we have given Bessa.
Are you going to transport heroin?
Now your friend will prepare you a nice dose.
I have to drive to Montenegro instead of Jole tonight.
Tonight.
They accepted me.
Dushitsa, my darling, may luck be with you! To Mom's heart!
Now Dad can't forbid me to study in America.
Come on, you can go faster!
Go, Bes!
Bes, slow down! I'm going to fuck off!
Mr. Berisha? Wait.
Accept my sincerest condolences.
Who was driving the other car? Some guy from Belgrade.
Is he alive? Where is he?
I asked you something!
He's here, at the hospital.
Dardan!
Where did you go?
Don't do anything blinded by grief. Now you have to be with your family.
Be strong! I'm with you.
Translated by AcePhil
Dinner is ready.
Driton, Bashkim. Come on, children!
Come on. Go to your rooms. Come on.
BESA
Episode 2 SUFFERING
Hello, sweetheart? Hello, love.
We're heading to the airport now.
We'll be there in two hours. How are you? I killed the girl, damn it!
Can you hear me? Here.
We're leaving now. Come on.
Come on, we'll see each other soon.
From Divna: " Dardan's daughter died."
"We're leaving for Belgrade immediately."
How are you holding up?
You have to be wise and restrained.
Don't do anything that would endanger us.
That dog Petrit is just waiting for that.
No one wants a partner who can't be controlled.
We'll talk about it after I bury my daughter, uncle.
Dardan!
Look at me. I can't.
Are we clear?
Have I ever deceived you?
Excuse me, but... here.
This is him.
Excuse me, please. My husband has had an incident. Uros Peric.
Follow me. Here he is.
You can't! Why?
Let me go! I have an order.
Please!
My love! Hey!
We gave him strong sedatives, and he'll probably sleep for a few hours.
My love!
That there is my best friend.
Do you know who Dardan Berisha is?
Belgrade
Divna, two emergency tickets for me and for Mirko to Montenegro.
And see what you can find out. Should I call Lekich?
Of course. This is my chance. Hello?
Hello, sweetheart. I'm not there. I'm landing now...
I know. Okay, darling, see. Don't worry,
Dad is a bit busy, don't get nervous, wait for him.
I can call you later. I'll call you soon. Bye.
My love. Hey.
What's up?
Damn it, I killed the child!
Come talk to the kids a bit, huh? What do you say? Come on.
Come out in front of me. He was probably driving at 100 km/h.
Hey, sweetheart. Come talk to Dad for a bit?
Come.
Hello, sweetie? Hi Dad, are you alive?
I'm alive. What are you doing? Everything is great, here...
We're getting ready for school.
How are you? Excellent.
I'm a bit... I'm a bit shaken.
I'm fine. Good.
Una? Yes?
I love you, sweetheart. I love you too.
What's up? We have a problem.
Montenegro Police Ulcin Police Department
Where are you, Lamia? How long do you plan to fool me?
Lamia, the experienced stallion is the best!
Oh, boss! Do you want coffee, brandy... What's happening with the crash?
Besianna Berisha crashed into the bus of some unfortunate person from Belgrade.
It's all her fault. And the Englishman? What was Dardan's daughter doing with him?
I wonder about that too. Tell Divna to call London and check on him.
And those four on the beach? Why didn't I receive the report?
Ah, it's not ready yet. We'll send it tomorrow.
We identified two of them.
Isa Sadriu and Ekrem Alic.
Cigarette smugglers.
Sadriu died of a heroin overdose.
And the little one shot himself in the heart, right?
We all know whose doing this is.
That's why would he kill some cigarette smugglers?
Try to find out. Should I ask Dardan?
What about putting pressure on his people? Afrim or Hashim?
On what grounds? You don't need grounds.
Call them for an informative conversation. And they'll respond?
If they don't respond, arrest them.
When is the funeral of Dardan's daughter?
Tomorrow. After the funeral,
bring in Hashim.
Pick up. I apologize.
Hello?
You need to work on your form.
And you don't need to be too arrogant, because Petrit wants to lock you up.
Who cares?
The boss wants an autopsy on Besiana.
And your traditions?
What do you care about our traditions?
The blood analysis is already done. Only for alcohol.
But the boss wants a full one.
Drugs, pills...
A full analysis. You know...
My dear, it will come out.
Fine, I'll try to get an order.
What order, idiot?
It has to be unofficial.
And you'll only tell the boss the result.
Hashim, only an idiot would ask that of me.
I am a member of the special unit of Interpol fighting against narcotics.
You're a member of the Special Squad at my job!
Mr. Perich, I apologize, but it's really necessary.
Oh, mate...
I wanted to say that my client is not a criminal.
Never convicted... You're right.
The problem is, he killed another participant in the incident.
And according to the law of the Republic of Montenegro,
we have to detain him for 48 hours.
I understand, but if you let us go to Belgrade, I guarantee you,
he will be available... Colleague!
If we let Mr. Perich go to Belgrade,
what do you think Dardan Berisha will do?
LAKE GENEVA
My condolences, Dardan. Be strong.
Thank you, Agime. God bless you.
I have no words. I'm in shock.
How is my sister? You can imagine.
Let me hear her. She doesn't answer my calls.
She's asleep. Good.
How are the boys? How do you think, Agime?
Yes, I can imagine. I have to go.
We'll try to come with Ilir as soon as possible.
Thank you, see you soon.
Yes, Dad? Call that moron.
Dad, sorry, but maybe now is not the time.
On the contrary, now is possibly the best time.
They know how to pay assassins, and we know the media.
Don't you want their killers to come here to us, Ilir?
I don't want that. Come on, son.
Okay. Fine, fine. No problem. Bye.
It was Divna, about the Englishman.
Just some nonsense on Ibiza with ecstasy and minors.
Nothing for us. We'll see.
After the Englishman, we'll visit the bus driver.
Tell management that we'll go after the funeral.
Right away. Let's go.
Inspector Petrit Koçi. Mirko Sandić. Interpol.
Was Besiana Berisha your girlfriend?
What? No!
We just went out together. Since when?
I don't know. A few weeks.
Did you know who her father was?
I know he's loaded. Is that why you liked her?
Damn you!
Besiana's father is Dardan Berisha.
The biggest drug trafficker in Southeast Europe.
Did she tell you about him? Have you ever seen him?
Him or any of his people? Look...
I had a gig on Ibiza. It got postponed, so I came here.
Bes was secretive. How was I supposed to know her dad was a gangster?
Was Besiana Berisha under the influence of drugs or alcohol?
I won't say anything more without her lawyer.
Why are you so hostile, Mr. Bay?
Think about what happened. And about all parties involved.
And then think about who would be on your side.
Yes?
The headline is "The Cancer of the Balkans." Dad wants you to leave for there right away.
Okay, I got it...
Look, I'm all about this...
See, the daughter is not the issue. The issue is the "cream" of the business,
which will be at the funeral. Okay.
Bye.
Don't worry about anything.
Good evening, Mr. Perich.
Inspector Petrit Koçi and Mirko Sandić from Interpol.
Mr. Perich? Are you sure the accident was an unfortunate incident?
What do you mean? It seems unusual to me
that you didn't notice the car on this straight and clean road.
I noticed the car. But I thought it would stop.
Did you kill the daughter of the biggest drug lord in the Balkans accidentally?
What do you mean? That I hit her on purpose?
Uroš, you are in great danger.
Especially if the car accident wasn't a coincidence.
When Dardan Berisha decided to retaliate,
Interpol might be your only chance.
And what does Interpol have to do with an accident?
With an accident - nothing.
KOSOVO MOUNTAIN RANGE
Mr. Braha...
Congratulations on your appointment!
Mr. Berisha sends you his congratulations.
Now that you are at the helm of the Kosovo Privatization Agency,
we will listen carefully to every word you say.
Mr. Berisha finds your conditions acceptable.
And he sends you a small gift. A vision for the future.
The future construction is in the national park. That's right.
You have too many national parks.
We will declassify this beauty and start building your
"Balkan Side of Wonders." Although, as you know,
I am obliged to invite more candidates. You might have competition.
As you know, Mr. Berisha can be very persuasive.
When will the auction start?
Together with our Serbian colleagues, we are trying to find
common ground to achieve our joint venture.
The agreed amount was transferred to your account this morning.
And you and your Serbian colleagues use the same bank.
Mr. Braha...
Uroš Perić. Born in Belgrade. 44 years old.
No criminal record. Married. Has two children.
Father - Božidar Perić, retired.
He owns a pharmaceutical transport company, "Pharma Trans."
The company has loans.
Is that all?
There's something else.
His brother was killed in '94 during the conflicts in Zemun.
It begins.
Hashim. Agim.
Where is your boss? He's waiting for you upstairs.
Accept my condolences.
Be strong!
Thank you.
Accept my condolences.
Be strong! Hang in there!
What a tragedy... I can't believe it.
It's hard when we lose a pure and innocent soul...
And on the other hand, those who don't deserve it continue to live.
Such a shame!
A sin!
A sin...
It's true.
Where is my sister? I would like to see her.
Agim...
Hey. Hey, don't worry.
Everything will be fine. Come on. I'm here.
Did you kill Dardan Berisha's daughter?
Which god sent you?
Your hand is gilded.
The father is a devil, and the mother suffers.
Dardan Berisha...
The shame of the Albanians!
I'm here because of him.
Do you know what Besa is?
I gave Besa to my Serbian neighbor
to protect his house in the city, because of the war.
And I kept it. A relative of Dardan wanted to take the house.
He told me, "Don't, don't"!
I killed him like a dog!
But that man can never return home, can he?
But that's not important, son.
The important thing is that I gave Besa.
That's what matters!
Come on, grandpa, get out.
You can't hide from Dardan.
And even at the end of the world, he will find you!
Both you and your family!
Mrs. Berisha, my condolences for your daughter.
Stop. He came to provoke us.
Do you know that I'm a foreign reporter?
Okay, okay!
This is too much! We will talk to the authorities!
God, accept her soul into heaven!
You're not normal! And what did he say?
That I love him.
Witty. And what was that with the shirt?
When someone from the family throws a shirt into the grave,
it means that the deceased will be avenged.
And why the lad? He's angry because he's a lad.
You know why.
And this is because you're brave and strong,
but never do anything on your own again!
Understood? Now go.
Speak!
I have the autopsy report.
Find the dealer!
Call Braha and tell him to release the driver.
Consider it done.
You get five, you get ten.
Afrim, my brother, you scared me.
Drive!
From Belgrade? Let's go.
Give me that. Here you go.
We sleep and we trade.
Isn't it suspicious that they released me so quickly?
No. It's not unusual. They can only hold you for 48 hours.
Let's have a beer. Let's.
You tell him. He'll listen to you. I have no problem with that.
I got my man back. I want to treat you.
You guys have a beer, I'm going for a swim.
Excuse me... Mr. Perich?
Good day.
Who are you?
Angelo Dini. Nice to meet you.
I'm from the press. Journalist.
For many Italian media. Just a little chat, if you may...
If you'd be so kind. I write about the tragedy,
that befell the most controversial businessman in this region...
And who are you? His lawyer.
Great. So the two of us will...
Okay, okay. Don't worry. I understand.
I don't want any trouble. Explain to the lady.
Okay. Sorry. Thank you.
I'll try to get some sleep.
The boss is looking for you.
I don't know why he's sleeping so much!
Leave him. Come on.
Cheers!
I'm going to wake him up.
Urose?
Milichak?
Urose!
Pavle! Urose is gone!
Are you the one who killed Besiana?
How is that murder? I didn't kill her!
It was an accident! I don't believe in accidents.
Someone has to pay! You, the driver who killed her,
or you, the dealer whose drugs ruined my daughter.
Boss, forgive me! I didn't know. I sold it to an Englishman, boss!
If I knew, I would have killed him like a dog, boss!
Boss! What should I do with you two?
Should I accidentally kill you?
Boro? Let him do something for me.
Kill the driver with your bare hands! No!
No, no, don't! I'm not guilty!
Hey! I'm not guilty!
Hey! I'm not guilty! I'm not...
Release him!
Translated by AcePhil