Previously:
Get ready, we're going to Kosovo.
Dardan ordered everyone to go to Kosovo. I don't want to live there.
Come to me for the weekend.
Everything should be ready in three days. Got it?
Since I didn't kill you when you killed my son-in-law,
and you brought my niece to take care of her,
it means I won't kill you now. I gave you my word.
And I gave you a grandson.
It's time to run.
Where do we run?
Where wouldn't Dardan find us?
Una, we can't see each other anymore.
Luka, please!
ROVIN
Which hotel did he say you stayed at?
Maria, I have to go to OUME.
You're leaving?
We'll talk later, bye.
Uki-Tuki.
And you have to say Ivek-Pimpek.
Ivan.
You look good, damn it!
No wonder you're screwing them all.
If I don't return in half an hour,
disappear!
Good morning, Hashim, hero!
Dardan betrayed us that night
when he didn't follow his order.
If you help us, you'll get
Dardan's place
and 10 million euros
in a Swiss bank.
Turn there, turn!
Calm down, I'll...
Listen to me, turn there!
Let's go.
Radivoje Bukvich
Arben Bayraktaraj
Milos Timothyevich
Lana Barich, Gresa Palaska,
Hana Selimovich
Mensur Safhiu, Radoslav Milenkovich,
Milan Marich, and others.
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
LION
Episode 8 TUNNEL
Good morning.
Where's the fire, Dukic?
Yesterday, Mehmet Agani was killed
in Rovin.
The owner of the "Adriatic Nord" company.
One water, please.
What does that have to do with us?
Probably nothing.
Except that Agani was an old friend
and associate of Dardan's son-in-law,
Agim Sokoli.
We're leaving!
Mirko, I want you to check
a murder in Croatia.
Mehmet Agani, right away!
Can I ask where he was?
No.
And what would you think if I showed up
with a gunshot wound?
I don't believe it,
and better not to know.
Oh, damn it!
What is this?
Antibiotics and painkillers.
I'm afraid the results
will disappoint you.
We're used to it.
None of the DNA samples
you brought us,
match those
from the crime scenes, which means,
none of these men
were there.
Of course, they may have worn rubber
gloves and been very careful.
I doubt it.
They are from the "old school."
And yet there's something
that may or may not mean anything.
And what is it?
We found the same DNA
on the genitals of the dealer,
on the clothes of the journalist, and in
the room where the DJ was killed.
That's it.
Thank you, sir.
Alright, damn it.
We're missing something.
Obviously.
What do we do now?
What if the same guy killed
Agani in Rovin?
And the three previous victims are connected
to the death of Besiana Berisha.
I really don't know what Agani
has to do with it.
I don't know either, probably nothing.
He's probably involved in something else.
Let's get going.
What's up?
I'm listening.
What do you want to hear?
The whole story.
Do I have to?
Come on, sit.
Greetings from the sea.
Received a postcard.
Let the driver rest one day,
then send him south.
Understood.
Seems like you fancy the driver, huh?
He'll become a man.
Let's go.
Goodbye. Have a nice day.
I can't get up.
You're vomiting a lot.
Thinking about it,
it might be better to die
than be in your place.
Boss, you were looking for me.
Yes.
Tell Enver to take the documents
and head to Kosovo with the bus.
Hashim?
Tell him.
Drive Teuta to the airport in Tivat.
Consider it done!
Afrim, get the car ready!
I want to go to the cemetery.
Understood!
Did you say goodbye to your mother?
Get up!
Be good and listen to your father!
Right? Mom will come soon.
Take care of your brother!
See you on Monday.
Where are you going, dad?
To the cemetery.
Can I come too?
Come.
Stop!
Be careful!
Let's go, we're leaving.
Go, go!
Watch your head!
Take him to the operating room!
Keep his head elevated!
Hold on!
His life is not in danger.
Let's take care of his wounds
quickly!
Let's go! Two at the front entrance,
two at the back!
No one goes in or out
until the special forces arrive!
Boss!
Damn it!
Is he alive?
They say he's alive.
They also say that the shooters
were uniformed, from your side.
If it's you, the city will burn,
you know that?
Easy, anyone can
put on a uniform these days.
No one in the police is crazy enough
to shoot Dardan Berisha.
You have all sorts among you.
We'll block the entrances.
No one steps in!
No one steps out!
You can't block the hospital.
It's full of patients, it needs to operate.
Go to the church and light a candle.
If he dies... you'll regret being alive!
One of ours shot him. But he's former,
dismissed for corruption.
Be quick!
They shot Dardan.
The attackers were wearing
police uniforms.
They're fighting for his life.
They've blocked the entire hospital.
Aren't you going to say anything?
Special forces to surround the building!
And don't take any action
until I arrive!
Understood, give me a second.
Alright, your flight to Montenegro
is in three hours,
you already have your ticket!
From Avdi: Agani is competition in the bid
for Brezovica. Call me.
Do you know what Mehmeth Agani did
before they killed him?
He submitted documents for a bid,
for that ski resort in the south.
Call our colleague in Croatia.
You're going to Rovin.
I'll call Mirko.
Where is my son?
Ma'am, please get out!
- Calm down, dear.
Will he be okay?
- Will you leave or should I?
Dear... I'm here.
Don't be afraid.
Calm down. I'll wait for you outside.
Come on, be strong.
How is Dardan?
He's in the operating room.
Luckily, he was wearing a bulletproof vest.
Who was it?
- I don't know.
Who shot at my child?
Who was it?
- I don't know.
Who was it? Who was it?
We'll find him even if
he's hiding in a mouse hole.
Find him!
- You come with me. We have work to do.
How many people do we have?
- Fifteen.
Block everything, stairs,
elevators, every entrance.
And not a fly should pass through the hospital
without my permission!
What if he doesn't survive?
- Excuse me?
Enver...
Look at them. See how they gather like wolves.
What do we do if they come in?
We'll keep them out, Enver.
We won't let them in.
Hashim, I respect Dardan a lot,
but I don't want him to die in vain.
Enver, don't forget
we've given our word, Besa,
to stay with him to the end.
Did you forget?
I'll damn them all...
Mrs. Berisha, the bullet
that went through him,
entered through the right cheek
and exited through the left.
That's the good news.
So, is there bad news too?
- There is.
The bullet tore off the entire
front of his tongue.
We stitched the piece we found in his mouth,
but...
The tongue isn't whole.
Will he be able to speak?
The bullet severed Driton's tongue.
Horrible...
And Dardan?
I don't know yet; he's still in the operating room.
He'll pull through, I'm sure!
I hope so, Agime.
I hope he pulls through.
But I won't pull through...
I'm completely destroyed.
Everything will be okay.
Okay? Can you bring back
Driton's tongue?
Hello.
- Where have you been?
Oh, wait a minute. Are you okay?
- I'm not, let's dig in!
I can't. I'm tired.
- Come on! Shall I take over?
Come on.
- You're hitting softly.
Come on, hit a bit harder.
- Harder, huh?
Go ahead.
Let me see!
Maybe you're not that tired.
- Sorry.
It's okay.
Dad?
Is he back?
Are you hungry?
- No, sweetheart.
You need to eat.
And I want to talk to you.
What's up?
- How was it in Banja Luka?
Work is work.
I'm exhausted from the journey.
Will you tell me what's going on?
- Why?
What should be happening?
Do you know that your mom thinks
you have a mistress?
I know. I know about it.
- You know?
Do you think we don't see
you falling apart?
Dad, look at yourself.
- Where were you?
Dad, you need to pull yourself together.
And let me tell you one more thing...
Why are you yelling?
Dad is back.
What's happening now?
Can you hear me?
I hurt my hand
while changing the tire.
Really?
- Really.
Why do you constantly lie to me? Do you think
I'm stupid? Where were you?
It's not what you think.
- What do I think?
That there's another woman? If so,
that's the least of the problems.
Haven't we agreed not to lie to each other?
- We have.
Then why are you lying to me?
Why didn't you take our car?
- I don't know.
The drive shaft broke, and I had to call
for roadside assistance.
They took the car, but they didn't have
the parts to fix it.
The damage isn't that light,
they said...
I can't... I can't...
Where are you going?
- I don't know.
What's the situation?
- We're waiting.
And the job?
- We continue as usual.
Someone will call you.
- Can I ask one more question?
Briefly.
- What happens if it doesn't get fixed?
I'll pretend I didn't hear you.
Okay, I didn't ask.
Your mommy's nasty, shrimp!
I'm listening.
- Darling...
What do you want?
- I miss you.
Something seems fishy, huh?
You have a new task.
I'm waiting for you under the bridge in half an hour.
Early this morning in Ulcinj,
an attempt was made on the life of
the boss of one of the strongest
criminal clans in the region,
Dardan Berisha.
According to unconfirmed information,
Berisha was shot
with automatic weapons,
three people dressed in uniforms
of the Montenegrin Police.
Berisha was taken to the hospital in Ulcinj.
Our sources report
that Dardan Berisha,
has died after receiving
six gunshot wounds.
but we still don't have
confirmation.
Yes!
Thanks! Thank you!
Where are you, Mima?
I heard that you're unemployed now?
But you're really dumber
than I thought!
You believe the media, huh?
You'll have to do some work for Mima too.
Don't lose your training.
The anger was only for Dardan.
Don't make me get out of the car.
Don't be cute; you'll get beaten up.
Did someone's balls grow?
From now on, forget I exist.
Is someone's ego inflated?
Don't force me to come down from the car.
Pedal, you wretch.
Where to?
To see if my nephew is alive.
Stay here, can't go any further!
Are you ready to die for this?
I am ready! Back off!
Oh, Skender!
Good day, I wish.
Since you said it, Spasoje.
Why did you block here?
You blocked the floor
of the hospital, and we're here.
We're guarding Dardan, and you?
You may
have shot at him.
Maybe.
But there's someone to check that.
Those in costumes.
We with the bulletproof vests only shoot.
Right?
Spasoje...
If it were your son, would something
stop you from seeing him?
Driton is alive.
Dardan is still in the operating room.
Now we can't do anything.
We're waiting.
Is everything blocked?
Yes.
Split the people into two teams.
You stay here during the day, and you at night.
Now go.
Understood.
You guard the door...
door... door... door.
Mrs. Berisha...
He'll live. We removed
several bullets from him. Quite a few bullets.
One more remains. For now,
we won't touch it
because it's between the aorta
and the vertebral column.
We'll wait for him to stabilize,
and that will happen.
The outlook is good.
Thank you, doctor.
Have a nice day.
What's the situation?
The hospital is cordoned off. They're not letting
anyone in. We have information
about at least 15 armed
individuals inside.
I will go in.
I want to speak with Skender.
Hello, Uncle Skender!
We haven't seen each other in a long time.
Very long.
We last saw each other
at our house in Pristina,
37 years ago.
I remember it as if it were today.
It was Bayram when you killed my father.
And now, what do you want?
I want you to withdraw your people.
The police should guard
Dardan and Driton.
And how do I know
you didn't order the attack?
There's no way to know...
But you have to trust me.
Once he comes to his senses, Dardan has to
give testimony, and so does Driton.
I guarantee
nothing will happen to them.
I don't trust you or the police.
And I didn't trust your father either,
even though he was better,
much better than all of you.
Is that why you killed him?
I killed him because we were adversaries.
But I respected him.
I respected him a lot.
You know I'll never
forgive you, right?
Never!
You have 24 hours to decide
what you're going to do...
After that, I'm coming with my people.
Sure.
Crystal clear.
You decide.
What are you playing?
Translated by AcePhil