You spill my blood, blood you shall return to me.
You will kill five people for me.
I'm familiar here.  And I need something unfamiliar.
Good night.
He offered to buy me another one.
A stranger will buy you a phone?!
He's not a stranger. He knows Dad.
Me?
Yes. And someone named Mima
sends you greetings.
Who is Mima?
I returned his son.
Come on, finish your job.
Congratulations on your new appointment.
Now you are the head of the Kosovo
Privatization Agency.
I think it would be fair
if I also benefit from this job.
Don't stick your nose in my business!
Period!
Very strange!
What's strange?
There are too many bullets.
Good day.
Good day, Mrs. Peric.
Inspectors Petrit Koci and Divna Dukic
from Interpol.
Is your husband at home?
Do you mind
if we record the conversation?
No.
Why are you recording?
Maria... Let people do their jobs.
Mrs. Peric, we're on your side.
If you don't want to talk
here, we can call you...
Please, feel free to record.
Thank you.
Mr. Peric, have you heard
that David Bey was killed last night?
Yes.
We believe it's a case
of professional murder.
And why are you telling me this?
Two weeks ago in Ulcinj,
Boro Zamovich was killed. Someone bit off
his testicles and beat him to death.
They left unnecessary traces.
What does this have to do with me?
Behind these murders
is Dardan Berisha.
There's a good chance
you're his next target.
Why do you think that?
Mrs. Peric,
both victims are connected
to the death of Besiana Berisha.
There's only one more left.
I won't be caught.
And why are you so sure?
That night, when...
when they released me from custody,
I was abducted by Dardan's men.
They wanted to kill me.
And? What happened next?
He gave up.  He learned that his daughter was
driving under the influence of drugs and...
It's quite unusual that
Dardan Berisha just let you go.
What do you mean, just like that?
They beat him up!
And you didn't think
it was necessary to tell us?
What were we supposed to tell you?
These are mobsters, and we're just ordinary people...
Dardan Berisha had a friendly chat
with David Bey as well.
And just a day after that, David Bey
was killed.
It's very important to understand
that people like Berisha
wipe out entire families
without blinking an eye.
And... Is that all?
Yes.
If you want, we can ensure
your safety.
There won't be a need.
And how will you do that?
We will assign police to monitor
your house 24/7.
Well...
There really is no need...
Why?
Maria, there's no need.
Mrs. Peric, thank you.
I'll show you out.
If you reconsider.
We'll stay in touch, Mr. Peric.
So be it.
Thank you for the conversation.
Have a nice day.
There's something suspicious about that guy.
Take your position.
Move!
I think we should accept
this police protection.
And then what?
We'll have to be guarded for a lifetime.
What do you suggest?
Should I take the kids to Split to stay
with our family and wait to be killed?
Is that it?
Did the biker leave?
He left,
but someone parked a gray Citroen
in his place.
Really?
Most likely.
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
ROVIN
Agime?
My dear Mehmet...
How's Rovin?
Everything's as usual.
Sun, sea...
And ice cream and lemonade.
Oh my God, you're living the life.
It's like Tito is still alive.
Brotherhood and unity.
You know there will be an auction soon,
for the ski resort in that southern mountain?
I want you to bid on my behalf.
I want you to fill out the paperwork
in the name of your company
and contact the Germans.
I'll finance everything, and you get
five percent of the profit.
Agi...
Don't I get only five percent of life?
Agi, please... Don't involve me in this.
I already have thousands of problems
in Croatia.
Is this how we talked when
you needed help?
Episode 6
NOISE
Hello?
Massage parlor
at "Karadjordjeva" 19.
Be there in half an hour.
I can't right away.
It'll be necessary.
Rajko Lalic. Chief
of Montenegro's MUP,
a general from the old school.
Tough, relatively clean,
has political ambitions.
Good day.
Thank you for coming.
Please sit.
As you probably already know,
things have become more complicated.
Wonderful, if you love.
Yes. Over the past three weeks
there have been several murders,
which we believe,
are ordered, perhaps even committed
by the Dardan Berisha clan.
We know about the murders, but we haven't
heard of any evidence.
General, you know very well
that the Berisha clan operates
very professionally
and there's never anything
to catch them on. And even when there is, they...
Remain inaccessible.
So, I have a new idea.
I've got support from Lyon.
Kotse, sorry...
But Raiko and I plan to watch
the Partizan match tonight,
and we also have a
social event on the schedule.
How long will this take?
We won't delay, I promise.
General, the problem is that I won't
succeed without your help.
I'm listening.
I want the Montenegro Police,
to conduct an operation to arrest
Dardan Berisha and his lieutenants.
On what grounds?
Taking DNA samples.
We hope
someone left evidence.
To me, Inspector, this seems
like a desperate move.
At the moment, we have nothing better.
And this will allow us
to interrogate them.
Maybe someone will give in.
General?
And when do you want this to happen?
Tomorrow.
We have international support
for the operation, and you have the people.
The only thing
that remains is the order.
And who will sign this order?
Judge Bazhdarevich. Your son-in-law.
Do you want me to put a stone
around my sister's husband's neck?
General, in Lyon, they are strongly
concerned about the fact
that the latest victim
of the Berisha clan,
is a British citizen.
Can I tell you something
unofficially?
Of course, tell me.
I wouldn't bet a penny
on Lyon or Europe!
Is that unofficial?
Thank you for being so honest.
Especially when your mandate is running out.
I heard that you'll be targeting
the Minister of Internal Affairs' chair.
A recommendation from the Interpol
headquarters would be beneficial for you.
General.
CAUSE
Hello?
Something interesting has come up.
Yes, I'm listening.
Today, the agency received
another set of documents
for participation in the auction.
From a Croatian company
called "Adria Nord."
They've built some large hotels
along the Adriatic coast.
Should I inform your favorite?
Of course. Immediately.
Are you sure?
Hans, you're becoming annoying.
Goodbye, sweetheart.
Mr. Braha...
I'm afraid we have a problem.
We're traveling to Montenegro tomorrow.
Okay, I have something to take care of.
And? What did the cop who visited you say?
He said I'm in danger because of
the accident I was involved in.
He's questioning me about...
Hey!
No names!
He's questioning me about your friend.
I told him we met.
And that he forgave me
when he found out his daughter
was driving drugged.
Then why is the police following you?
What police?
You have a tail - a silver Citroen.
A package will be waiting for you at the office.
Call me when you open it.
You're a genius! They unlocked us...
I'm going to the accountant. Mira.
Mehmet Agani
Montessori Street 50, Rovinj
Ivan Tadic
Rakovica, Belgrade
Did you open it?
Why do I have two passports?
One for abroad and one for the hotel.
Leave your phone.
The one in the package
has a Bosnian ID. Tell your wife
you're going to Banja Luka.
You leave tonight.
You'll see, Rovinj is great!
Swim there for me.
Kisses!
ULCIN
Thank you, Lamia.
Montenegro Police
Arrest Warrant
List of individuals to be detained:
Dardan Berisha, Enver Ramadani...
Thank you.
I have a question.
Yes?
Why me?
Because you've got balls.
That way, my kids will feel at ease,
lifting me in the air.
That won't happen.
From now on,
Mr. Lekic is responsible
for your personal safety.
He's no longer part of the Interpol team
and can fully focus on you.
Yes. That's what I was afraid of.
If something happens to
Mr. Bazhdarevich and his family,
I'll personally hold you responsible.
If you say so.
How many times have I told you
never to touch it?
Do you think that makes you a man?
No! It makes you this.
Kelesh.
Stop, police!
Drop the gun!
Hands up!
Don't!
We're not cowards to surrender.
Drop the gun,
We won't surrender, Dad!
Listen to your father.
Give me the shotgun.
Like this.
Here.
The little one will have to come with us.
The little one won't go anywhere.
Hand me your weapon.
If you touch him, he'll bleed.
You know that, right?
Or should I come with you peacefully?
Why are they in handcuffs?
- Do you regret it?
It's not by the rules.
You'll keep them for half a day
until the lab technicians arrive.
And you think about
what Enver and Hashim will say
when someone whispers to them
that the idea was yours.
Don't they pay you enough?
Are you leaving again?
I have to go to Banja Luka.
I have a meeting with the director
of the clinical center.
When are you coming back?
- In two days.
Can I come with you?
I've never been there.
What about your work?
I'll take leave.
I can't take you.
I have a lot of work,
I don't know these people...
I can't take you.
Let him not see the messed-up
police and the mafia, and...
You keep disappearing,
coming back beaten! I'm tired!
I can't live like this anymore!
I'm tired of living like this!
I'm tired!
Calm down, Maria!
- No, let me go!
Calm down!
Calm down, please!
No.
Calm down, it's necessary.
I have to go, for us,
for the company. Calm down, please!
Hello, Dardane.
This is Dr. Mitrovich.
She came to help society.
Be afraid.
Now the doctor will take a sample
for DNA analysis from you and your brothers.
There's no way you haven't left
some evidence.
And this...
Do you know him?
- Can you?
Open your mouth.
I heard you want to get involved
in a legal business?
To develop our skiing potential
to a European level!
And your cases will be handled
by Adnan Braha. - Shake hands.
It's not easy for you.
Your daughter is a drug addict,
your sons growing up as criminals.
You resemble each other.
You look a lot like your father.
And he, like you...
Until Skender cut his throat.
And others say I resemble him.
Except my father didn't believe
in blood revenge.
And you?
Do you believe?
MISHA
Hey, where are you going?
- Hey, I have a problem.
I need your help.
- Seriously, you're freaking me out.
I'm traveling, and I need
your car for two days.
Why don't you go with your own car?
- I can't explain it right now.
I'll tell you later.
Brother, you'll have to explain
this and a million other things, you know?
When I come to you.
Does 15 minutes work?
Well, let's go.
Did you bring my coupon?
- I broke it. Give me a cloth.
What do you need my car for?
- I have to go to Bosnia.
I messed up big time.
No one should know.
Understand?
- Misha, I can't tell you anything.
It's for your own good, trust me.
- I'll explode soon.
and take your secret to the grave.
Let's say I killed a person.
Even two.
Oh, I lied to you, brother.
Three.
I'm kidding. I lied to you.
Please don't tell me anything
until you're sure I'll explode.
I have to go, come on.
- Here's the key.
We'll see each other in two days.
Take care.
Damn it!
Good evening.
Authorization
How can I help you?
On what grounds is Mr. Berisha
and his associates detained?
Your clients are detained
because they are criminals.
They are suspected of committing
very serious murders.
And that within only
a few weeks.
Let's put speculation aside.
Do you know they can't
be interrogated without a lawyer?
Absolutely. If we had interrogated them,
you would have been present.
We just took DNA samples from them.
So, can they go?
- Of course.
Tomorrow morning. When the legal
24-hour deadline expires.
Good evening, Mrs. Peric.
- Good evening.
Do you have a few minutes?
- For what?
Can we have a drink somewhere?
I need...
I need a bit of your time,
I want to show you something.
Look, I've been on my feet all day
and really have no strength for any talks.
Maria...
It's about Uros.
What should I do?
- Well, nothing.
Nothing?
- Nothing.
Maybe you got used
to doing it like this?
Or otherwise.
- How?
Like this or otherwise.
Doesn't matter?
- Doesn't matter.
Does it bother you?
- Not for me.
But for you?
- For me, yes.
For you, yes, but not for me.
- And not for you.
Not for me. And for you?
- And for you, yes?
For me, yes. And for you, no.
Won't you undress me too?
I'm listening.
Do you know where
your husband is right now?
Excuse me, but I don't understand.
Why do you care about that?
You don't want to answer
my question?
What does it matter to you
whether he called me or not?
Your husband parked his car
in the "Delta City" parking lot,
went inside, and hasn't come out.
His car is still there.
My question is,
do you know where he is?
He went on a business trip.
Without the car?
He probably took one of the company
vans, I don't know.
Has he called you?
I can't understand
what this interrogation is about?
What do you care
whether he called me or not?
He might have a lover.
He might have 7 lovers,
in 7 different countries! Is that a problem?
Is that a much smaller problem
than the one you have right now?
And here we are talking about
the safety of you and your family.
Thank you for the coffee.
Maria, I'm not your enemy.
Goodbye.
Hello?
- Hello, it's me.
Hey, what's this number?
Bosnian.
I forgot my phone in the office
and had to buy a new phone
and a new SIM card.
Where are you now?
Well... on my way to Banja Luka.
Are you using the bus?
No, I'm driving our car.
Why do you ask?
Well... nothing. Just asking.
Maria, is everything okay?
Is Viden awake?
He's sleeping, and she's with a friend.
Listen, I'll text you when I arrive.
I love you.
Okay, bye.
Come over.
I can't.
I don't want to go home.
Okay then.
No, you'll come home now.
Let me smoke.
Will you call me tomorrow?
Are you really not going to call me?
You're lying!
There's no reason for me to call you.
I'm kidding.
Go to sleep, what's wrong with you?
Come in.
Bye.
Do you know what time it is?
I was at Natasha's. Good night.
Natasha called your home phone,
your mobile was off.
Where were you?
I was walking in the park.
You're punished not to go out
for a week.
Good night.
Fine. Good night.
Come in.
Do you want something to drink?
If you treat me.
I have some wine.
Dry, red.
Where were you?
With friends.
And? What were you doing?
Nothing, we were watching football.
Football?
Really?
What's wrong with you?
What did we say about the little one?
What are you doing with her?
Nothing.
Huh? What are you doing, damn it?
Damn it?
I'm not!
If I see you with her again
I'll kill her!
Drishlo!
Damn it.
This is the blood of David Bey.
Translated by AcePhil