Previously:
We're close.
Close to what?
Close to the edge.
Can I come to you?
Of course.
Welcome to Serbia.
How are you?
I'm looking for these two. One has
a scorpion tattoo on his hand.
Do you want to play?
Football?
Interpol's red bulletin.
You shouldn't go.
This is not your job.
It became my job
when he mutilated my son.
Imagine a situation where
someone would give you a huge sum of money,
to continue your work,
just change the company.
It's one thing to protect your loved one,
and quite another to expose
your children to danger.
Please!
Give it to me.
It's me, can you hear me? Don't worry,
I'll call you when I can.
Your brother convinced me.
He can be very persuasive.
Don't do that!
Is it Mima?
It's Mima.
Dardan Berisha.
You can't catch him,
but he harms our business.
And who are you?
The Sokoli Clan.
I'm sorry I wasn't
a better wife to you.
They took a DNA sample for analysis.
Don't think about that.
Attention, intruder on the third floor.
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
Lake Geneva
Episode 12 SKY
Welcome, little sister!
Well caught.
Where is Ilir?
He's around here somewhere.
Let's have coffee.
These are his fake passports.
And this is the Bosnian phone.
He had it with him
when he killed Agani in Rovinj.
He called his wife
from this phone.
And this is a disk,
with pictures of your man.
It will be useful to you.
And what's this?
No, no, no.
This one is mine.
My communication with him.
Don't screw me over, okay?
Who would screw such a handsome man?
Dardan worries me.
It's like he's lost his way.
And you told me, and people talk.
Let them talk.
We lost our daughter.
People always talk.
That's right.
But it's not good for our business
to talk too much.
Sometimes words
are more dangerous than bullets.
And did you find out who shot him?
And you? You said you would do everything
to find the culprits.
Auntie, welcome!
Ilir's wife is pregnant.
Congratulations!
Hopefully, when he grows up,
he'll be as handsome as Driton.
Really?
How is this possible?
Evidence from the crime scenes?
Everything is destroyed?
Everything?
Thank you.
VILLAGE IN KOSOVO
Eat. Rest.
You leave in two hours.
Vetum Leka, from Lyon.
Ordinary, family man.
No criminal record.
And he stormed the laboratory
with a clear conscience, right?
The French police say
he explained his actions as
temporary insanity, but the point is
that his wife is from Kosovo,
from the Berisha clan.
What are we going to do now?
Nothing.
Uros Peric is a free man.
All evidence has been destroyed,
even the crime scene clues.
The warrant has been withdrawn.
They are ahead of us again.
But maybe we can
get ahead of them?
Do you think Agim is next?
Why don't we try to stop him?
I'm not sure.
As much as he hates Agim,
Dardan's wife is crucial to him.
He wouldn't kill his son-in-law,
because it would risk
his clan falling apart completely.
Okay, then who?
Who's next?
There are several candidates.
There are even some in the privatization fund.
Plus Cimer.
Plus Agim's son, Ilir.
There are quite a few.
Alright.
I'll call Avdi, arrange
discreet security for Cimer in Pristina,
and you... call Vienna.
Put a tail on Elsa.
Hey!
Inspector Koçi...
I feel like you do.
What an unfortunate coincidence.
Do you think it's a coincidence
that Leka's wife is Dardan's cousin?
For years I've been telling you
that the Albanians operate within a family circle
and you can't apply your strict
police rules to them.
For months I've been hearing about laws,
procedures, and rules.
You should be ashamed of the position
you're taking!
VIENNA
Have you finished, Inspector Koçi?
Yes. There! My weapon!
I'm resigning.
Wait! Wait!
Listen... I'm sorry I didn't give you
more support.
What can I do to help
with your investigation
to put an end to the Berisha clan?
Call Vienna.
Put Elsa Fischer
under police protection.
A Balkan gangster
and a European Parliament member?
Miss Fischer is connected to this
major privatization,
through the new director of the Kosovo
Privatization Agency.
To put someone of such high rank
under police protection,
a strict procedure must be followed.
You need to send me
a detailed report,
with which I...
Your pistol is here, in the holster.
Mima is guilty of everything.
So now they're looking for the fugitive?
No.
Now what?
You do nothing. Go home.
See your family,
and I'll find you later.
And what will you do?
I have to finish something.
Inspector Koçi!
What do you want?
I offer assistance.
I know about the destroyed evidence.
Sit down.
Should we negotiate dressed?
What do you have for me?
Where did you get this?
Is that important?
It is important.
It is important to decide whether you will
use it to get to Dardan.
And in return?
Be a little more enthusiastic.
And if you can't, then you're looking for...
Who arranged the weapon
and passports for him? I want him!
There, you see? You can be
enthusiastic.
He is with us now.
But I can't give him to you.
We will get him out of the country.
Agreed?
A deep moral dilemma.
I'll leave all this to you.
Even if you don't want to
cooperate with us. It doesn't matter.
You don't want to screw me.
You don't want to help me.
I might start to appreciate you soon.
Despite being a stupid jerk.
Teuta! Sister!
I'm coming.
I am very happy; with me are
my son and daughter-in-law Aferdita.
And my dear sister Teuta.
A person with such relatives
and friends is a rich person.
Cheers!
I am pregnant... both Ilir and I
will have a baby.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Can I say something too?
Of course, sister.
I would like to say a few
words about our family...
...the wonderful Sokoli family...
And for my dear brother, Agim.
Thank you.
You probably think that now you are safe,
now that you are part of the Sokoli family?
You are safe only as long as
you please my brother.
You are safe only until
he betrays us.
Teuta... what are you saying?
Agim organized the assassination
that almost killed my husband
and seriously injured my son.
That's enough!
Word for word, Besa for Besa!
VIENNA
I'll have to cancel the meeting
on the board. Freeze the auction.
You won't cancel anything.
We have to act as if this
has nothing to do with us.
No, I'll call the police.
And what do you plan to tell them?
That this maniac wants
to kill us all.
And so you'll connect us all with him?
In the election year? Our careers
will die just like Agim's.
Do you understand that?
Go home.
Everything will be fine. In this story,
we are on the side of the law.
On the side of civilization.
Far from that wilderness over there.
Fine. See you tomorrow.
Goodnight.
BELGRADE
Do you want me to give you your jacket?
I don't want your jacket.
I want to make a toast
to my new employers.
And why don't you take your phone
and dial the number?
To brag in person. I just need
to bring more first.
Check the time for me.
What are you doing?
Playing chess.
And who's winning?
What are you doing here?
Luca, come on! Go home,
I'll call you tomorrow.
Go.
Well, exactly as we discussed...
What's happening to you!
Didn't I tell you to...
Hello?
Jon?
I'm coming.
I want to tell Mom about us.
I want to introduce you to her.
Why?
Because I love you.
Wait here. Okay?
I'll wait.
Mom...
Milichka.
What's going on?
I want to introduce you to someone.
Okay.
We have information that Mima has worked
with the Dardan clan.
Interpol Vienna.
Call them.
Hello?
Yes?
Thank you very much.
We have a new murder.
In Vienna.
Hello?
Agim?
When?
Yon isn't answering his phone.
I don't know where he is.
I understand.
If Ilir says so, I'll leave for Geneva immediately.
Hey, come on!
I'm done with this.
There's no point anymore.
What does that mean now?
Tomorrow I'm resigning!
Alright, wait, calm down.
This isn't the end of the world,
you've given everything...
And what?
Is that supposed to comfort me?
For years, I've been running the office, and? Where are we?
Give me one name that we have?
Uroš Perić.
We only need one piece of evidence...
And what if we have evidence
against Uroš Perić?
Why, what if we have evidence?
Are you messing with me?
Can you hear me, what I'm asking you?
Huh?
What are you suggesting?
Should I hand over the evidence?
To have them destroyed,
like they destroyed the DNA samples?
No, to use them,
to catch that guy!
I don't understand,
why are you giving up now?
And what will we achieve with this?
We'll put Uroš Perić in prison and?
Will someone new kill for him?
I don't care about Uroš Perić!
Do you understand?
I came to Interpol to destroy
the Berisha clan and catch Dardan!
But you don't want to catch the man
who kills for him?
He's an indirect victim.
So he's innocent?
You don't understand...
You don't understand!
All this time, I've been following you,
because I believe you're acting right.
I can't believe you've hidden
evidence against him from me!
These people killed my father!
They slaughtered him like a pig
in front of my eyes.
I want him. Personally, Dardan!
And I'm not choosing the means anymore.
And what are you suggesting?
To hand over the evidence?
Either you follow the law
or you're with me.
You need to come down.
People are waiting for you. They're coming
to offer their condolences for Teuta.
And until when?
And you know yourself,
our work never ends.
I'm tired...
Right now you need to be strong.
Be strong? For whom?
For Teuta, whom I'm burying...
For Besiana, whom I buried...
or for my maimed son?
This is the price of the work
we do.
I didn't choose this job.
And you know that very well.
Dardane,
we all pay the price for this life.
Ilir will catch up with us soon.
Ilir, Agim's son?
If he dares to come after us, personally,
I'll kill him with my own hands.
And what about Interpol?
After Elsa's death, Petrit will have
the green light to come after us.
Why?
What have I done?
Have I killed someone?
If there's evidence,
arrest the driver in Belgrade.
Dardane, listen to me!
You listen to me.
And hear me well.
I want you to withdraw from everything today.
After Teuta's funeral,
say that you are sick.
Take my sons and lead them
to a safe place.
Give me your word,
that you will protect my sons!
I entrust their care to you.
You go.
And your affairs, I will finish... alone.
You know,
I won't leave you alone,
until you tell me what's happening?
You already know everything.
So... it's true?
Four murders.
One for each of you.
For Maria, Viden, Una, and for you.
You are foolish, foolish...
Do you think,
that the monster
will leave you alone now?
I will come down here.
Stop here.
Come on.
Wait!
Yes?
You know I've been through a lot in life.
And that you can count my qualities
on the fingers of one hand.
But I'm good at one thing.
I'm good with weapons. And that's why...
From now on, I want you to involve me
in everything that happens.
Is that clear?
Come on.
We'll talk tomorrow.
Here, a little more.
That's it.
See you tomorrow, right?
Okay, yes.
When I get back from basketball. Okay.
We understand each other.
Come on.
Give me the joint.
You shouldn't smoke!
And you shouldn't kill...
Thinking...
my life wasn't bad.
Well, it wasn't.
We had a great time.
Everything will be okay.
Coupon is waiting for me...
Hey.
What's up?
Misha died.
It's over.
I paid my debt.
Now you are safe.
That's the most important thing.
Dardan can't do anything to you anymore.
And you?
Translated by AcePhil