Previously
Why? What kind of method is this?
Blow up a person's grave? You have to admit, it has style.
Could at least be a little more discreet.
Call that idiot.
"Cancer of the Balkans." That's the title.
Dad wants you to leave for there immediately. Okay.
Look at this jerk, what nonsense he writes!
Our media pumped him up? All of them.
Dardane. The driver is not the problem.
He's the solution.
"Driver, how is it at home?" For whom?
For Chelsea. Read my lips.
I shed my blood, blood, and you'll pay it back to me! You'll kill for me 5 people.
One for each of them and then we'll be even.
Give me Besa.
Here is your Besa!
Urosh Perich. Mima.
I bring you a gift from Ulcinj, this package.
Hello? Urosh Perich is calling.
ANGELO DINI
Sit down.
Do you want to fuck first or talk?
Whiskey? Sure.
Come on. I'm listening.
No need to be scared. Relax. This is just a regular interview.
Here you go.
Coke, do you want? No.
No? I knew it.
Family man. All the cocaine is mine.
I love this country!
Freedom is here. For example, this little bitch here,
do you know who brought her here? Her mother.
This is business. Do you have children?
And you, what do you care?
Well, I'm just asking. Do you have them or not?
I have a son. He's big.
If you had a daughter, you wouldn't talk like that.
Bravo! What a specialist you are!
Speak, please. Everything.
How did it come to this misery?
Where is your restroom?
What's up, Perich? Are you sick?
You need to disappear.
Save yourself while you can.
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
Mishi robe, give me the pizza here!
Episode 4 FALL
Una? Someone might have spit in your pizza.
If it's the mouse, I'll beat it up!
And what if it's me? Then I'll eat it.
Here you go. Remove my mushrooms.
Remove them yourself. What's this?
Here you go, dad.
Look, fool! Shut up!
Damn dog. Shut up, damn it!
Dad!
Come on, eat! We only have an hour to play.
Come on, hurry up!
What have you done?
Good.
Okay, didn't she want to break up with him herself?
And now she's mad that you didn't leave him first.
What does it matter? He's an idiot!
Half the day plays games, the other half watches porn.
Who does that?
Believe me, it's better this way.
How sweet she is, right?
I'm going to light a cigarette.
Mima. Hey, it's me.
Tell Dardan I couldn't do it.
Didn't I tell you not to use names?
I'm just an ordinary person, not a killer. I can't kill.
Can you hear me?
This man has a wife and son, damn it!
I couldn't shoot! Okay.
So everything else, just not that! Do you understand, everything? Please!
Can you hear me? Good night.
Hello? Your mother...
Hello, tell me? Hello, Divna?
I have unusual information from a reliable source.
Two pathologists from Pristina went to Ulcinj a few days ago.
They performed an autopsy on Besiana Berisha.
What autopsy, I don't understand. Why wasn't it done by our pathologist?
Because it was an unofficial autopsy, requested personally by Dardan.
The drug king tests his late daughter for drugs?
Don't worry, I'll investigate. Greetings from Pristina.
Then I'll call you. Bye.
Excuse me, darling.
Can I get a kiss?
Shkodra
Welcome, son-in-law! You found us well!
Hello, little sister.
How are you?
Like a dead person who still walks and breathes.
I can imagine...
Go and settle in.
We won't take much of your time with your husband, we just have something to take care of.
Thank you for coming... in such a difficult moment.
He called me to talk face to face.
Here I am.
I need to tell you something.
I hope you won't get angry.
Hey, sleepyhead! Come on, get up!
I'm going to buy some things for the celebration tonight.
It's your birthday! Happy birthday!
Thank you. Will you take Viden to school?
I'll take him. - Come on, please. And call Una.
I need her. She should come right after school to help me.
I left her a message, she's not answering. - Okay.
And she's making scenes of jealousy! - What jealousy?
I can't believe what's happening!
Finally, she came to the cafe to see who I'm sitting with!
I believe you. - She says, "I'm uncomfortable too,
but wait a minute, you can endure. You need to know that Milos is gay."
And there's nothing... there's nothing for me to explain who is what.
Okay... Okay, are you listening to me? - I'm listening to you, wait. Sorry.
Come on, pick up that phone. - I can't, my battery is dead.
I've called you a hundred times, it might be important. - What's important?
Should we throw a party for the birthday? It's turning three hundred!
Well, go help her. We'll see you after three hundred years.
We'll talk later! - See you later!
From Mom: CALL ME. IT'S URGENT.
Such an idiot! - Are you okay?
Do you want to kill me, for God's sake? - I'm sorry, please!
He's broken. - How wouldn't it break?
Okay, I'll buy you a new one. - I don't want you to buy me anything.
So I'm Luka. - What?
Luka.
Una. - Nice to meet you, Una.
Otherwise, Una, you should know that this is not a pedestrian path,
but I'll take responsibility for my actions.
I know. I know both.
Whether I'm guilty, or it's not a pedestrian path?
Both. - Okay, okay.
What can I tell you? - Nothing, be careful how you drive.
Can I at least take you for coffee?
Because of the experienced stress? Please.
Brandy Skanderbeg...
Good as its creator.
Yes.
You know, how much I respect you...
and appreciate how you treat my sister...
Drive straight!
That dealer.
It's not done like that anymore. - I have nothing to do with it.
There's talk that this scumbag sold ecstasy to our little Besiana.
Please!
Don't listen to everything people say.
I am broken because of her death too, but that doesn't mean we should be killing people on the streets.
Because that way, we'll destroy our families.
We'll destroy our business.
My dead are my concern.
Don't stick your nose in my business!
Except for a big deal that we need to understand.
Brezovica.
We've reached an understanding about Brezovica.
You own it and the consortium managed by my company.
Yes, that's right. To some extent.
Our business is separate.
Except for a big deal. We need to talk about it.
Brezovica.
We've reached an understanding about Brezovica.
It belongs to me and the consortium managed by my firm.
And that's final!
I think it would be fair for me to benefit from this too.
Let's say about 20%.
And in return...
I propose to help you by taking care of all potential buyers
who could be your competition. You want to help me?
Are you messing with me?
Big deals require big friends.
Think about it.
Boro Zamovich. Escaped from Byalo Pole.
Last year, a member of his gang tried to liquidate him.
Since then, he's been selling ecstasy at sea. Autopsy. I knew there was something.
If you drive at 100 km/h on a dirt road and you're not insane,
probably there's something else.
Don't forget something? I didn't.
Wounds on the testicles and bite marks,
you mean to say this doesn't fit the mafia?
We don't have an explanation for that. We don't,
but maybe we need to find out who ordered the autopsy?
It was probably someone from the hospital or the police.
Exactly. Let's go.
MIMA
Hey! Oh, goodness!
Did I scare you? No.
How was school? It went somehow.
Did you play football? Yes, I scored only four goals.
MARIA
Come on, get in.
Hello? Did Una call you?
No. She was supposed to be back from school
two hours ago. Who knows where she's wandering again?!
Dad... Dad? Tell me, son?
Why are you upset?
I'm not upset.
I'm just a little worried that Una hasn't called.
Thanks for the drink. No problem. Thank you.
No, thank you for breaking my phone.
Alright, I'll buy you a new phone. I don't need a phone, really.
No, I insist. No, really. I don't need it.
Fine.
But you can give me a ride home.
Thank you. You're welcome.
Let's do this... Yes?
I'll give you my number, and you can call me if you change your mind.
Alright.
Have you considered my offer?
For the brandy?
I think it's excellent.
As for Brezovitsa... forget it!
I was talking about the brandy.
But it's good you mentioned Brezovitsa.
Goodbye. Who is that guy?
Who are you riding with?
What, should I take the bus for two hours?
How do you know he's normal? You hang out with strangers.
I'm not hanging out. And it's your fault for the rest.
What fault do I have? Una!
What Una?! How are you talking to us?
She sent me a hundred messages! I was responding to her while crossing the street.
I could have died if he hadn't stopped! Alright, nothing happened.
Where's your phone? Here it is.
It's broken.
He offered to buy me a new one. A stranger will buy you a phone?
He's not a stranger at all. He told me he knows Dad.
Me? Yes. And he sends regards to someone named Mima.
Who is Mima? Who is Mima?
Mother, whatever I heard, I'm telling you.
Who is Mima?
Where are you going?
I'm going... I'm going to the office, I forgot your gift.
Listen to me.
If you have any problems, come to me!
Don't mess with my child!
Don't get involved with her! Fine,
we don't need you. We'll take care of the little one.
Carefully with knives, with roosters. And you'll watch!
Hello?
Here.
It's you again. Didn't I tell you
you have to run away from here?
Alright.
Let's do an interview then. I see you're a very dangerous person.
What are you watching?
What's up, Perich? What are you waiting for?
Come on, shoot!
Shoot! You're not capable of that.
You punk! Look me in the eyes!
Tell me, why didn't the boss send Hashim, but you?
Get lost! I'm disgusted by you, you coward!
Go!
Take me home. Tie me up,
That sweet Una of yours.
Sweet little devil...
Good evening, everyone! Oh, good evening.
Hello. Hi.
I apologize for the delay.
Hello, my love. Happy birthday!
What's there to drink. You have some explaining to do.
I lost the gift somewhere. Damn it. You know...
Do you want cake? No, thanks.
We received an urgent order for quick assistance.
There was no one else to take her except me.
When a person has a perfect marriage, they can afford to be late...
For their wife's birthday. Play something.
Escape attempt?
Otherwise, it will be unlawful detention on your part.
I have grounds. But I rely on your discretion.
I thought the police preserved the innocence of a man.
As if you were unpleasant.
Sex between colleagues doesn't count.
And Todor?
I don't sleep with mafia dogs!
He brought Albanian doctors to perform the autopsy.
But that's your problem now.
Lekich!
Where are you, boss? Do you want kebabs?
I'll have to ruin your meal. If you have to, ruin it.
The autopsy on Besiana Berisha was organized by you.
And it's your responsibility for the dealer's death.
And surely you have evidence for that?
You travel around Europe, spend European money.
You've been chasing Berisha for two years, and then you come here,
to tarnish the honest and honorable Todor!
From this moment, you are suspended. I may not be able to put you in jail,
but I will do everything possible to throw you out of the police.
Don't you want kebabs?
I see that you're better, Mr. Bey.
You are free to go.
And now where to?
What's wrong with you people? I'm a patient, not a damn prisoner!
Am I accused of something?
Thank your consul. He pressured our ministry to release you.
Personally, I would keep you here until I find something to accuse you of!
I have to go to damn Belgrade in a few days. There are no direct flights from this hole.
Bazhdarevich!
Do you smoke weed? Shame!
Good weed, man. Local, Albanian.
It has a wonderful taste.
I'm 99% sure it's Dardan Berisha's merchandise.
Have you tried his heroin? It's mind-blowing.
I don't use. Why not?
What kind of DJ are you then?
What about MDMA? LSD? Ecstasy?
Are you finished? I would like to leave.
A few days ago, Dardan Berisha ordered an autopsy on his daughter.
I believe he found something in her body.
Dardan is trying to find the culprit for his daughter's death.
If they found something in her body, I have nothing to do with it.
See, my friend, I believe you... but will Dardan believe you?
By the way...
We found your friend, the dealer, on the beach, castrated.
Damn it!
What time is it?
Why didn't you wake me up?
Wait, wait.
Hey, watch out! You're defending. You're not defending.
Me? Yes.
Come on, it's your penalty. Are you ready?
Let's go. Like this.
Well done! Just a little bit. Football is bad.
Did you eat anything? No.
It's a diet. Who's on a diet, huh?
Little mouse! No!
Very good! Well done!
Go get the ball. And apologize to the neighbor.
Go for the ball.
Why did you decide to call me? Did I surprise you?
Well, yes... So, are we going to buy a phone?
You're very bad if you think so.
I'm kidding. You know what...
I want to see you.
Well, come then. Bye.
Move it this way.
Where's the money?  I don't have any money.
Is that how it's going to be?
Put his finger here!
Give your finger! Give your finger!
Thank you, darling.
On Monday. The deadline for the bank is expiring.
You forgot. No, I didn't.
Mrs. Kosanovic, "kidnapping" is a strong word.
Don't worry, I'm solving the problem and will call you back.
Someone has to work, you know?
And I work, it's just that... It's like I'm not working.
Save me, brother. How much?
Six grand. Three installments on the loan. Uros, how long will I keep saving you?
We'll see each other tonight.
TIVAT MONTENEGRO
Good evening, Mr. Bey. Mr. Berisha wants to talk to you.
I'll miss my flights.
He has arranged private transportation for you to the airport.
Translated by AcePhil