Previously:
Whoa!
Good day, Ivan Bilic!
I talked to Uros
to tell you everything.
What will you do
if someone ruins you?
Did he tell you? What did he say to you?
Do you know who studied with Ivan Bilic?
Who?
Uros. Uros Peric.
Ivan Bilic was killed
a week ago in Rovin.
We think that he and Mehmet Agani
were killed by the same person.
I haven't been to Rovin,
haven't seen Ivan,
and now, if you please,
either let me go,
or allow me
to talk to my lawyer.
Mr. Peric, do you have any objection,
to giving a DNA sample for analysis?
We want to confirm
that you're not involved in Ivan Bilic's murder.
What murder?!
I have nothing to do with these murders!
In that case,
let us take a sample and you're free.
Let me go!
If they see us together,
they'll scatter us. Got it?
I don't care!
Coming.
What's happening?
I'm leaving for Kosovo.
What were you looking for at home today?
What did they sing to him?
Listen, if that psychopath
comes to our home again, he'll kill you!
What did they sing to him?
Police!
Clear!
Where is my daughter?
Interrogation of Maria Peric
in connection with a criminal case,
for which her husband, Uros Peric, is a suspect.
Mrs. Peric, where is your husband?
Last calls:
Luka
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
Episode 11 BLOOD
Leave!
Enver!
Hello, driver!
How are you?
Great?
How are your relatives?
They are alive.
My daughter is not.
And now to work.
What does Petrit ask you?
Petrit knows I was in Rovin.
And what did you tell him?
If I had told him anything,
I wouldn't be here.
Or maybe you did tell him.
And both you and Petrit
play some game.
Maybe it's like that.
If you think so,
it would have been most reasonable
to kill me right there, on the spot.
Enver.
What did he sing to Petrit?
Come on.
Enver.
You don't have much left. We're close.
Close to what?
Close to the end.
But this time it will be
a bit more complicated.
How else?
You're good, driver!
You're good.
See you soon.
Just one more thing...
They took a DNA sample from me for analysis.
Don't think about it.
I want a phone.
Where are you going?
Drive!
Where to drive? Why don't you pick up...
Please, just drive!
Are you crazy?
Welcome to Serbia.
How are you?
You're a driver. You stay silent and drive.
Nikola Tesla Airport
Belgrade
Good morning, my boy.
Good morning, uncle.
I haven't heard "boy"
in 30 years...
Let's play.
I missed this.
Alright.
I have news...
They're not good.
Agim included his company
in the auction for Brezovica.
Damn.
That European bitch,
didn't she warn you?
No.
Apparently, she believes Agim
is the stronger player.
We'll see.
It'll be a shame one day
when you regret
knowing something
but not telling us in time.
It's one thing to protect your loved ones,
and entirely another to endanger
your own children.
Sit there.
Excuse me?
Sit there! Why are you looking at me?
Sit!
Give him the shirt.
Fix his hair.
Glasses.
That's good.
Good-looking.
Hello!
I'm Mima.
You have a feminine name.
And you have a funny accent.
Yon.
Like the accent, so is the name.
Do you speak Albanian?
A little.
I understand more.
Where are you, Luka, bro?
Looking for someone, bro?
I'm looking for these two.
This one has a tattooed scorpion
on his hand, see?
Maybe he'll fall for a knockout?
Is the new five stolen?
You could say that.
You could say...
I'll find them. Is it urgent for you?
No, bro, I owe you my life.
Take it.
Hurry up.
I'll call you.
Can I join?
If you're that pretty, you must.
Hello.
Mom's golden.
This is my sister, Ana. Mima.
I know.
What do you know?
You're well known among us.
Sit.
You work for one of our countrymen.
And now, what?
Well, let's talk,
for a hypothetical situation.
Come on.
Let's imagine a situation,
where someone would give you
a huge sum of money,
to continue your work,
just by changing the company.
What would your response be?
Well, since it's only hypothetical,
it's hard to say.
But if the amount is seven digits,
in euros?
If it wasn't hypothetical,
I'd kick your damn ass! Got it?
Calm down. We didn't mean to offend you.
Please, check
your bank account.
Where did this money
come from in my account?
From the boss.
Who's the boss?
The boss is Agim Sokoli.
Are you aware
that you're playing with death?
Control over the entire
territory of Serbia.
A percentage of the profit. And your hands
will be untied.
Think about it until tonight.
If not, nothing for anyone.
Hypothetically, we were talking
about seven figures.
And in the account, I see only six.
The seventh digit depends
on your answer.
Hypothetically.
If you agree, call me.
Block all border points.
Yes, I'm ordering. Yes.
For two months, this guy
has been in front of me.
And I let him kill
and escape.
What are you doing here?
Red Interpol notice.
Divna, go to Urosh's father.
Okay.
And you visit his friends.
Just let me ask you something.
Searching for:
Hidden Number
Hello?
Who's calling?
My name is Ana.
I want to meet you.
Why?
Because of the one you're looking for.
In half an hour, in the café
in Dorćol.
You'll forgive me.
It's hard for me to believe this.
And yet, you reacted
as if you believed.
When was the last time
you heard from your son?
A long time ago.
And you don't know where he is now?
No.
My older son...
my late son.
You know well who he was.
And how it ended.
And Urosh has always been somehow...
Soft, like his mother.
I've always said, son, Urosh...
Damn it!
I messed everything up.
And you?
Do you have children?
A daughter.
Female children. Only female children.
Do you want beer?
No, I can't, really.
Thank you, but I have to go.
Let's share one?
We can share one.
Here, you forgot your phone
in the room.
Agim.
Hello, little sister.
How are you?
How is Driton?
He realized he won't be able to speak.
I spread a rumor. I'm looking for the villains.
Find them!
God help them when I catch them!
How is Dardan?
Physically, he's okay, but...
Mentally, it's a wreck.
He doubts everyone... even me.
I have no words.
Agi, I can't take it anymore.
Can I come to you?
Of course. Will he let you?
I think so.
Anyway, he neither looks at me
nor talks to me.
What about Bashkim?
I want to come alone,
to get away from everyone.
When can you send a plane?
Whenever you say.
Can it be tomorrow?
I'll tell them now.
Take care, I kiss you.
Take care.
You shouldn't go.
I've told you a hundred times.
This is not your job.
It became my job when he
maimed my son.
Dardane.
You know I've never wanted
anything from you.
That's right. You haven't.
Now I do.
I'll go even without your permission.
I know.
Don't doubt it.
Then why are we discussing it?
Because I respect you.
And...
The children?
Driton is no longer a child.
Bashkim knows he's Berisha.
He'll get used to it.
And you?
Who are you?
Your wife.
Hey!
Una?
Come look at me, darling!
Look at me, baby.
Look at me, hey!
Una?
Una, please look at me!
Damn it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's do this,
I'll sit with you. Is it okay?
Is it okay?
Come.
Give me a cigarette.
Please!
Come on, I'll buy you ice cream
if you give me a cigarette.
We're not fighting now, okay?
Please!
Give it to me.
Do you want to play?
Football?
Football...
Shall we play?
Come on.
Hello?
I'm coming now...
You walk too confidently.
You liked everything I did for you.
Have you decided?
I think so.
Your brother convinced me.
Yes, he can be very persuasive.
So, until tomorrow?
You won me over.
Hello?
Hey, it's me. Can you hear me?
Don't worry about anything,
I'll call you when I can...
Go there!
Get lost!
Montenegro Podgorica
Ulcinj
Call your wife.
The number is Kosovar. She's there.
Call Petrit.
I called him. No answer.
Belgrade Beginning
Kosovo
Ana Klimendi.
Sit down.
It's clean.
Let's talk about something
that concerns us.
Dardan Berisha.
You can't catch him,
but it's a problem for our business.
And who are you?
Sokoli's relatives.
Agi Sokoli's?
Mrs. Klimendi, I'm an inspector...
I know.
Chenge. And I am a miss, and I have a business proposal for you.
What should it be?
Nothing. Thank you.
I have information about the person
you're looking for regarding the murders.
And he will lead you to Dardan.
And in return?
Just be flexible
when transporting our goods.
This would be the perfect
moment to leave.
Before I arrest you.
Your inefficiency
has become legendary.
Don't be offended.
Can I ask you another question?
Well, try.
What will you be doing tonight?
Goodbye, Miss Klimenti.
Where was the call made from?
I don't know, they spoke
very quickly,
but we know for sure
that it's somewhere in Kosovo.
Tell Avdi to check with
the border police.
One of the Germans was there.
And?
It's about Hans Zimmer,
53 years old, a lawyer.
Respected member of the
German Democratic Party.
Works as the director of the privatization agency,
appointed by the European Parliament
and Elsa Fischer,
who is the leader of the Austrian Young Party.
One of them arranged with Dardan
for an auction, for Mehmet Agani.
One of them, both of them are blaming Dardan
for the auction, for Mehmet Agani.
And boom - murder in Rovin!
Write to Interpol colleagues
in Germany and Austria to check them.
Where in Kosovo?
With Dardan?
It doesn't make sense to be with Dardan.
It also doesn't make sense to kill
everyone involved in the death of his daughter.
Let's put that aside. We'll focus
on Uros's victims.
The dealer who sold her ecstasy.
The Englishman who most likely
made Besiana take it.
The journalist
who discredited Dardan.
And the man who participates
in the auction instead of Agim.
Who's next?
According to this logic, Agim.
Only if Perich is Superman.
So these are the Twins.
Jole and Mare Cholovich.
You owe me another 200!
Well, Mare has a tattoo on his hand.
Yes, that scorpion.
Now they're at "Bonbons"
with some girls.
It's all for you, bro!
Come on, we'll talk. Bye.
I'm not uptight.
Is that so?
I'm serious.
I'll see you.
Yes, you will see.
Come in.
Come on, get out!
Get out!
Drive! Drive, drive!
Fast, fast!
Don't do that, man!
Don't do that!
Come on, let's talk.
Let's understand each other.
Luka!
We're not going to fight now
over some chick!
Don't! Don't!
Don't, man! Don't!
Don't, Luka!
Damn it!
Is it Mima?
Work, bro…
I'll fuck your mother!
Run, fuck your mother!
Go away, your mother!
Your pussy mother!
I'll fuck your mother!
Fuck your mother!
Is it Mima?
Mima is the whore I fucked!
See how he lapped my cock! Tongue,
I didn't take a picture for you, your mother!
Let's go!
Is it Mima?
It's Mima.
Sleep, sleep, my son,
who washes your diapers?
Your mother washes you,
beautiful, the biggest...
I'm sorry…
…that I wasn't a better wife to you.
Forgive me for not giving you
a normal life.
I failed.
Translated by AcePhil