ADA BOJANA MONTENEGRO
BELGRADE SERBIA
BESA
Episode 1
THE ROAD
The little beasts are up!
We're coming, enough of lazing around!
Are you having sex again?
What else should we do?
Aren't we going to have breakfast today?
No, today the Peri膰 family is on fasting and prayer!
The little one can't fast and pray,
so get up and make us breakfast!
The maid Maria Peri膰 is on it.
Maid Maria, hurry up!
Yes!
It has grown a bit,
I would say in the middle of the head,
Soon you'll need to shave it bald.
No! We'll sell the vans and get ourselves a convertible.
Let the wind blow through your hair as you drive.
It'll be great fun!
Stop playing with that
phone on the table, please!
I'll stop when I'm done.
Please, stop right away.
I'll stop when I'm done!
And why aren't you eating?
My head hurts.
Don't lie, kid!
I can't go to school if my head hurts!
Don't you want us to call an ambulance?
Have them take you away on a stretcher?
And you, don't eat so much bread!
Why, what's wrong with him?
What's wrong with him?
Look at this!
He supposedly does
push-ups, but none!
Murder of a
high-ranking police officer in the province!
Alban Ko莽i, chief of
criminal police in Kosovo, has been killed.
War for the drug market in Gnilane,
Kosovo, July 8, 1997
Interpol
Inspectors: Petrit Ko莽i,
Divna Duki膰, Mirko Sandi膰
The Berisha Clan
I have results.
Sead J邪ferovi膰 arrives today
in Pristina and will testify tomorrow.
We've attached the best from the unit
for the protection of witnesses to him.
We've learned the names of these two.
Enver Ramadan.
And Afrim Deda.
Deda is a relative of Dardan
on the maternal side.
Call Pristina and find out
everything about these two.
Mr. J邪ferovi膰, we need to leave.
We're leaving in three minutes.
Three minutes!
Understood!
Don't touch!
They lifted him in the air.
Inspectors
Petrit Ko莽i and Divna Duki膰.
Jovi膰.
Ko莽i.
The bomb was under the car.
It is activated remotely.
Are there any survivors? No.
Who was driving the car?
Minich.
One of the deceased.
They were good people.
They'll weigh on your conscience,
you understand, right?
The safety of the witness
was your responsibility.
Why didn't you check the car?
Listen, tarikat!
Minich baptized my child,
he was my godfather.
I'm sorry.
I believe you.
But that's the work of those of yours.
And who are his?
The shippers.
And here I thought, Jovi膰,
that we're all one here.
And I think we're done here.
I saw everything.
I'll call Premovi膰
to convene an emergency meeting.
Do you think he sold out?
Cops wouldn't kill their own colleague.
So you think he's just an idiot?
I'm sure.
Any way you spin it,
we're in the shit.
ULCINJ MONTENEGRO
Alright. How?
Take it all.
Move, damn it!
Be reasonable.
Alright, goodbye.
Was it Enver? Did he finish the job?
That son of a bitch from Sand啪ak,
now he's going to God, let him be a witness, damn it!
Oh, your dirty mom!
Come on, hands up!
Do you bring good news?
What are you hanging there like a limp dick?
Come here!
Sit down!
Hi boss, how are you?
I have a business proposal.
You and business? Don't talk nonsense!
I really want to work for you.
And I want to fuck Rita Ora,
but it's not happening.
Well, I don't know what to say.
You know my relative, Isa...
He started smuggling
some guys from Albania.
And where did you learn about that?
He called me to drive the motorboat.
Tonight, 15 kilos arrive from Shkodra
and he wants to take them to Italy.
I told him:
"Don't do anything stupid, no one dares
to work behind Dardan's back."
If you mention that name again,
I'll kill you! Do you hear me?
I'll tear your head off, you understand?
Sorry, sorry. I dropped out.
What happened, asshole?
Did you shit yourself?
I told Isa:
"Don't do anything,
the boss will fuck you up."
And he says to me: "I'm my own boss,
I don't give a fuck about everyone!"
Hashim, won't you say a good word
to the boss for me?
God help us, boss.
He'll help if we keep
to the agreements.
I know, I forgot last night.
I'll wash it now.
Hello, people!
Hello, boss.
How's your wife?
Like a little elephant. She's rolling already.
So, like you? Emira?
Did anyone pay anything?
Nothing, boss.
And the bank?
The installment is in five days.
Oh, that's a disaster!
It would be.
If it weren't for the order from Montenegro.
It will cover the loan,
there will be money for salaries.
Excellent!
Come on, let's go, let's go!
Catch it as I pass! Come on!
Come on!
Watch it!
Come on, watch it!
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Come on.
Bravo!
Damn, three against two is nothing!
They're not that good; we're just bad.
The chubby one wasn't running at all.!
Here's the beer! I was done
with basketball, find someone else.
Misha...
Hey, you!
What's up?
What's going on?
My foolishness struck again.
Lymph nodes.
How? Everything was fine, right?
Oh, fuck the mother...
Wait, wait...
It was, damn it, but not anymore.
And now what?
Now biopsy...
If something's wrong, which it's not,
I'll be back in the hospital...
...full program.
Everything will be fine, brother.
Everything will be okay!
It'll be okay next time!
Enough of the nonsense.
Koci! You look good.
Look at him, fit as a fiddle.
That's how it should be, son.
And since I'm not operational,
I look like someone's grandpa, damn it!
And what can I do for you?
How is it that your people
failed to protect
the only witness
against Dardan Berisha?
A bomb under the car!
Who would have guessed?
If you had included me in the security,
the man would still be alive.
We deliberately chose the team.
Brussels may mourn the death
of a few locals,
but your death would have been...
If I let you interfere
with operational work...
... I risk a lot.
You risk more
if you don't leave me alone.
You're Albanian, right?
Paternally.
My mother is Serbian.
And my mother is Slovenian.
But that doesn't help me in Ljubljana.
Not a single Serbian cop
will want to cooperate with you.
For one year, so much...
Let's get to the point, General.
If we work together, I will lobby for you
in The Hague and Brussels.
Son, do you know how much
I don't care about The Hague and Brussels?
Mr. Premovic, you are appointed
directly by Brussels, right?
Exactly.
So it would be good to be friends.
And very bad if we aren't.
Especially after the death
of a protected witness.
And now what? Shall we kiss?
To start with, it would be good
to cooperate, General.
I don't know why you keep carrying
stuff when you have everything.
Maria sends her regards.
Thanks. How are the kids?
Growing.
They forgot how you look.
Shall we shoot a bit? No.
If you hit all four bottles,
I'll give you 500 bucks.
Drop it.
You dare to try, huh?
Let's make a deal:
if I hit, you quit smoking.
And if you miss?
I'll buy you a carton
for every miss.
That's four cartons,
I'll have enough to smoke until the end of the month!
Let's see you.
What's with the weapon taking?
You're endangering not only your own,
but also others' safety.
You're disrupting my concentration,
Major, huh?
Military psychology
in modern conditions,
page 63. "Breaking the
enemy's military morale."
See,
how well I raised you?
That's why I did it.
Because you raised me well.
Quit smoking from the 1st.
How's it going?
It hurts!
It needs to hurt a bit.
Come on, pull it up.
Come on, sweetheart, pull it up.
Come on.
I can't anymore! Please, don't!
Tell her, please!
She has nothing to tell me,
Sister Bilya is a great friend of yours,
but you don't want to limp, right?
Come on, pull it up!
Come on, pull it up again. Like this.
Enough, that's enough...
No, one more time. One more time.
Come on.
A moment of rest.
Do you know what kind of break I'll give you?
Come on!
There you go, see it's happening. Good.
Good.
Well done. Well done, you!
Take a little rest, and then again.
SPLIT CROATIA
Hello, Mare, dear!
What's going on with you?
Nothing, everything is fine.
What else can happen?
How are the kids?
He's great.
And she's a disaster,
doing whatever she wants.
I wonder who she's after.
And how is my son-in-law?
He's good. You know him, right?
Always aiming high,
but he's good at everything else.
How is it in Split?
What are you doing?
We went out for a stroll.
See the sea.
Is the tank full?
Don't worry, this boat has loaded
half of Montenegro with cigarettes.
Isa!
Where are you going, lad?
Come back, it's Hashim!
Hashim? Is that you?
It's me, brother.
Did he get scared of me
or this broad?
I'm transporting cigarettes to Italy.
I know, I know. Come, come.
Don't you know that my boss allowed it?
Come on, don't be a bitch!
Get up, get up!
You have to get used to these things.
I rewarded him. Now he's peaceful,
but he flies and is happy.
Don't be afraid.
Wipe your mouth.
Listen to me now.
I knew you were a good boy,
but this much, I didn't believe!
Thank you, Hashim.
I hope now you'll say a kind word
about me to Dardan?
Fuck your mother, boy!
I told you a hundred times not to mention
that name, damn it!
He was as dumb as an ass.
And he had no idea
what he was getting into.
Come on, boys. Move.
Pick up these crates
and throw them there!
Come on, quickly, move!
Let's go, come on!
Hello?
Tell me.
Yes.
And what's happening with Jole?
Damn it!
Okay. Nothing.
I'll be there in half an hour.
Come.
What's up?
Nothing.
Mira, Jole's wife is giving birth.
What does that have to do with you?
You're not going to deliver it, are you?
It has something to do with me.
I have to drive instead of Jole to Montenegro.
Tonight.
Come on, Mr. Peric. Here we are.
Come on, I'm leaving.
Come.
Kiss the kids when they wake up.
Come on, bye.
Bye.
What's up? Oh!
Come on. I love you.
Come on. Bye.
LION FRANCE
INTERPOL
Sead Jafirovic, he was a protected witness
in the case against Dardan Berisha.
Berisha controls 30%
of the heroin traffic,
originating from Afghanistan into Europe through Turkey.
He imports drugs into the region with impunity.
He's associated with extortions, human trafficking, and murder.
We know all this, you know all this,
yet he remains a free man. Why?
Because he's supported by corrupt government officials.
The Berisha clan absorbed vast amounts of Kosovo capital after the Balkans conflict.
We believe that they're using this money
to bribe local politicians,
judges, and police officers across the whole of Eastern Europe.
The clan is doing business with similar organizations
in Macedonia, Bosnia, Montenegro, and Serbia.
In 10 years, Interpol has not been able
to bring a single witness to testify against him.
Some vanished, others simply changed their testimonies.
Some, like Seat Jaferovic, were murdered
while they were on the police protection.
So everything produced and smuggled out of the Balkans
by the Berisha clan is received and distributed
into the West by the Sokoly clan,
Led by Agim Sokoli.
The two clans were united by Berisha married Sokoly's sister to create a blood tie.
In truth, it remains an uneasy alliance,
which, despite this marriage, could still lead to war between two clans.
We must stop Dardan Berisha before that happens.
Also, we have BESA to deal with.
BESA?
It's a code of conduct.
BESA is an Albanian cultural precept,
Usually translates to "faith"
which means to keep the promise and word of honor.
But within the Mafia clan,
breaking the BESA means certain death.
We understood that the budget increase
would be used for buying intel,
for forming a network similar to the one
that this organization has.
You intend to bribe politicians, judges,
and police officers, Inspector Kochi?
To fight fire with fire?
No, I don't think that's what the inspector is saying.
Then what is he saying?
That he needs more money.
If you give me these extra resources,
I will bring Dardan Berisha to justice.
Stanford University
Congratulations
Mom!
Tell me?
Come quickly!
Stanford University.
They accepted me.
Congratulations.
Mom's heart.
You look like who you are, my daughter!
Now dad can't forbid me
to study in America.
Sweetheart, Dad worries
that you'll live there alone.
How don't you understand, Mom?
I have to go there!
On the contrary, darling. I understand you.
I'll talk to your father.
I'm leaving.
Hey...
When will you introduce me to the Englishman?
Never!
Kotor Bay
Hey, did you arrive?
I reached Kotor Bay.
You can't imagine
how beautiful it is.
Is it more beautiful than my Split?
Nothing is more beautiful than your Split.
Yes, yes, don't think about it.
What are the boys doing?
The little one is washing my car,
believe it or not.
I don't know whose child that is!
I'll check if he has a fever.
But I don't know her. She's wandering around
or she's with Natasha. I don't know.
Come on!
Let the child live his life.
Why are you getting worked up?
He'll be 17 just once.
Alright.
Call me when you arrive.
Alright. Bye.
Bye.
Drive carefully!
No, no, no, no.
You scared?
No.
I don't want it.
Trust me.
Come on, you can go faster!
Come on, Bes!
Show me what you're really fucking made of.
Faster, faster, come on.
Bes, Bes, slow down, I'm going to fucking shit myself.
Mr. Peric, I am Inspector Lekic.
And this is District Judge Bazdarevic.
We have come to take your statement
regarding the incident you were involved in.
Can you talk?
What happened to the people
in the other car?
The boy will be fine, but the girl...
Come on people, leave the man alone.
Can't you see he's not well?
Thank you, Mr. Peric. We'll talk again.
Translated by AcePhil