Besi, calm down! You'll get angry!
This is him.
What's up? We have a problem.
If I let him go to Belgrade,
how do you think Dardan Berisha will react?
They lifted him into the air. He's connected to torture,
human trafficking, and murder. Plus, we have Besa.
Call the frog. If they pay you killers, we'll pay the media.
"The Cancer of the Balkans," that's the headline.
My father wants you to go there right away. - Okay.
My condolences. Thank you.
The boss is looking for you.
Uros? Pavle? Uros is gone!
Boro! Kill the driver with your bare hands!
I'm not guilty! Hey! It's not at fault!
I'm not...
Uncle, did he arrive? You shouldn't kill him.
Why? Dardan, let him go.
You know he's not guilty.
He's just a poor guy. I saw the blood analysis.
I didn't see anything.
If you kill him, everyone will know it was you.
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
Episode 3 CRACKS
Look at this, how much nonsense he writes!
Have our media burst him?
All of them. Read!
"The funeral of the young, tragically deceased Besiana Berisha,
was a first-class social event in this part of the Balkans."
"The criminal elite of the region,
rushed to honor the deceased daughter of the head of the Berisha clan."
"People from the most corrupt government in Europe,
came to pay their respects to the man..."
"At RAQA, who with his bloody hands rules Kosovo and Montenegro,
and controls the entire drug traffic to Europe."
"The fact that this man and his friends with dubious capital
will soon privatize everything that is worth something,
clearly shows the darkness that this region is sinking into."
Damn him, I should've cleaned him up!
And I just kicked him out.
To kill at a funeral?
What they write...
It only applies to Agim.
It's definitely his doing.
I'll kill them all.
Both the driver and the Italian journalist.
I'll call Mehmed from Munich. He's fast and reliable. He works well.
At this moment... a hired killer?
When we have Interpol on one side and Agim on the other?
This is madness.
Dardan!
The driver is not the problem. He is the solution.
Better use him.
I don't see another option. Only this one.
Mare... Should we go to the police?
My love!
Let's go home.
It smells so good, and you're still cooking!
How are you? Somehow.
Won't you tell me? What?
What what?
Where were you that night?
I don't know why you won't tell me.
It was a misunderstanding.
I got kidnapped. Kidnapped?
It was a misunderstanding? Who kidnapped you?
The father of that girl. Why didn't we call the police?
We left without telling the police. I'll call Pavel.
You won't call Pavel... Why?
Because I don't want the mafia to come knocking on our door.
Who knows what these people will do to us now?!
Nothing will happen to us. If they wanted,
they could have killed me that night.
We're safe.
Daughter-in-law, it was fantastic! And nobody praises me!
Oh, praise her! Otherwise, see what will happen to you!
Come on, enjoy a little more. What are you grumbling about? Eat.
I'm eating, can't you see? She's anorexic.
Don't be like that. Leave your sister alone. Tell me,
are you still for OFK Belgrade? What OFK?
I'm for Chelsea now. For who?
For Chelsea. Read my lips.
Unknown number. You have a message.
C-H-E-L-S-E-A. Chelsea.
Hello, driver. How's home?
Didn't I say that too? He didn't say that...
Chelsea from Marinkova is asking! No, it's from England.
What was the name of that footballer, a small one, shaking everyone up?
Come on, grandpa. Leave the kids to have dinner.
I won't cook for you anymore, since nobody is eating!
How can we not eat? You're just talking; the dinner is ruined!
I eat as much as I can! That's why you're so skinny.
Driver!
Come, come closer.
Don't be afraid. I won't do anything to you.
Come here.
How are you?
Family dinner?
Family is the most important thing in the world.
I would do anything for my family. And you for yours?
I also would. I believe you.
You have Maria, Viden...
Una... Is this your father?
Bojo, right?
Choose!
What should I choose?
Spill my blood, and I'll return yours!
Hard. Is it hard, huh?
Won't you give?
It's hard for me too!
Look...
I'll give you another chance. You'll kill five people for me.
Kill for yourself. And can you kill for them too?
One for each of them, and then we'll be even!
If not, you know what I have to do!
Kill me right now. Let's end this.
I don't want to kill you.
I'll let you live and watch. Hashim!
He says he tracked your daughter to the school.
He could have fooled her, but don't worry, for now, he has only watched her.
Shall we knock on the door and have a little fun?
I have to tell you, Afrim is a good guy, but a little crazy.
And he screws anything he gets. Come on. No, no, wait... Stop, hey...
I'll do it.
I'll do whatever you want.
You're a reasonable person. Let's see what kind of killer you are!
Okay. So if I do what you want,
you'll leave us alone?
You have no choice. You have to trust me.
Trust you?
You'll have to.
Give me Besa.
You want my Besa?
Kill my daughter, and you want my Besa?
Here is your Besa!
Driver?
Be ready!
Son or daughter? Son.
Boss?
I'll leave on my own. Enough of this nonsense, Jole!
Your wife is giving birth. Who will drive today to Vršac?
I will. Come on, get going.
Take care.
I have to tell you something.
But don't get nervous.
They called from the bank. We're behind on the loan installment.
We don't have enough in the account for both the loan and the salaries.
First, pay the salaries. And the loan?
I'll talk to them.
Good morning, inspector! Good morning.
How are you?
Boro Zamović, an old acquaintance.
He's been in the force for 10 years, which is a third of his life.
Beatings, extortion, drug trafficking.
For whom? For brothers, relatives, and friends.
But that's about you. Up north. And what is he doing here in Ulcinj?
Ulcinj is a tourist town. It's full of people.
Someone beat him up. Dardan's people.
Someone bit his left testicle.
Gentlemen, I also want to nail Dardan, but...
This is the work of some jealous wife or some crazy person.
Mirko.
What is this? A warrant for Hashim's arrest.
Hashim? Watch your balls, Todor.
Are you okay? What?
You've lost weight. Thank you for noticing.
What did you find out about the deceased? Nothing important.
He was a small-time dealer, Montenegrin. Down towards Ulcinj.
I wonder, what does this small-time dealer have to do with Dardan's dead daughter?
Yes. And what does the blood analysis of Besijana Berisha show?
I think she wasn't tested.
Only for alcohol. And now it's too late.
Learn what you can about this Boro and the Zamović brothers from White Field.
All right.
I shouldn't have divorced, I should have shot him!
I need to go get the child. How is she?
She's fine. We'll talk later, okay?
You three are so little.
Mom... can we play a little now? Okay, but put on your headphones. Okay.
Go.
This won't help. And what will help?
Besian's death is vengeance.
God's punishment for the dirty deeds you and my brother are involved in.
My brother and I are doing what needs to be done.
It's not like that. Think... Think well. We have enough money.
Think well... We have enough money.
Maybe it's time to start a normal life somewhere else?
You know very well that you can't leave this business.
You knew that even when you married me.
Are you saying when I was married off to you?
I didn't mean to offend you. You haven't offended me.
Agim called me.
I'm leaving for Shkodra tomorrow. Come with me if you want.
Here, Maria sent you your favorite Croatian stew.
Great!
Life is good, old lady!
What's good about it?
Why, what's good? Both of us haven't even hit fifty yet,
and we already have a new best friend.
Death, brother. Death.
It hit me in the lymph nodes, you in the brain...
I almost died in Montenegro. My wife acts like a detective.
The bank is squeezing my balls. I've never been so stuck...
Are you okay?
Misho?
Breathe! Misho, come on! Breathe, damn it!
Come on! Are you okay?
I'm fine, brother. Every day, I add a little gas.
I feel it growing.
It doesn't matter, a little more and it'll be over.
Do you think we'll have time for another basketball game before I kick the bucket?
Like this, with my pajamas, shooting a three-pointer to loosen my ass?
What... have you already made peace with life?
You talk like a dead man, but you're alive!
You're alive, and as long as you can, you have to fight this crap!
Don't give up, live!
And what do you think?
That if you argue with cancer, will it run away?
And you... what did you start to say? I interrupted you.
Nothing.
Call Todor.
He's calling me tomorrow morning for an interrogation at the police.
Petrit ordered it.
Go. Okay.
Todor is offering his, as he said, "sincerest apologies."
Damn policeman.
And you... be peaceful there!
Behave yourself.
Did you prepare things for the driver in Belgrade?
Of course. Do you want me to do something for the Englishman?
No. We'll wait.
Did you and the mechanic decide to be with us?
By Monday, we have to pay all the installments with interest,
Otherwise, they will initiate forced collection.
What are we going to do? I don't know.
I'll borrow from someone. I suppose.
Someone is waiting for you in the office. He owns two pharmacies in Vršac. Wants to talk business.
Good day. Uroš Perić.
Mima.
You're sweating.
Come in. Thank you.
My secretary said you have two pharmacies in Vršac.
I don't have any pharmacies.
I have a gift, this package. With regards from Ulcinj.
Milica, open the box!
Open it!
Now you have my phone number.
The address is on the back of the photo.
You have until Monday.
Why? What kind of method is this? To blow up someone's grave?
Now everyone knows that the mole has no peace even in the grave.
What do they know? That you're crazy, that you don't care about anything?
Don't talk like that, for God's sake, you'll destroy your family, your business, everything.
Agi is only waiting for this!
And when people find out? And what if they find out?
And Brezovica? What about Brezovica?
We've talked a hundred times that we need to leave something great for our children.
Only then will we prove that we have been someone and something.
Am I the problem? Me?
Do you think I'm crazy?
Uncle, do you remember what he asked of me,
when they locked you up, and my brother Ramu was killed?
I remember. I was only 17.
With my own hands, I buried my brother.
And on whose shoulders did everything fall when they killed my brother?
All the work, all the responsibilities... fell on me.
If I hadn't been so crazy, Agi would have taken everything from us.
He would have left us with empty hands.
Listen, uncle!
You're my uncle, I love you and respect you,
but don't come here anymore to tell me what to do.
Dardane, you didn't understand me.
I'm not telling you what to do, but as God, I beg you,
to take account of yourself. Just that.
Don't worry. I'm taking account of myself.
We know you killed Boro.
And those other two in the bay.
We also know that Enver lifted the protected witness into the air.
Now we just need to figure out which one of you idiots left your DNA at the crime scene.
Do you know what I don't understand?
What do you gain from all this? Hashim, how does this sound to you?
How does this sound? Sounds good!
Hashim will soon own half of Kosovo, and you?
I have nothing. No wife, no kids.
Are you a fag? Dardan's fag?
The lab report will show your traces, not his, Hashim.
But I have a proposal.
Give testimony against Dardan. You'll become a protected witness.
And you'll choose where you want to live.
You love dicks, right? A black one, a Swedish one, choose!
I suppose I want a black cock!
Or a cock of some Viking?
What? Didn't we establish that I'm a fag?
Give me a cigarette. I feel like smoking.
And?
How does that sound to you? It sounds good!
But it just sounds!
And do you know what sounds better? What?
Shall I tell you, or...
Tell me.
Tell me!
The story sounds better of how your father shit himself in fear,
before our guys cleaned him up.
It happened that they had to kill him shitting.
Like a dog.
You can go.
I said you can go.
Clean that up.
I came to say goodbye.
I'm going back to Kosovo. So fast?
Dardan! I won't stay where I'm not useful.
Come with me. Here, no one knows who's drinking and who's paying.
You have a wife and sons to take care of.
I buried Besiana here. We'll bury her there.
Hello? Yes?
Yes, yes, I hear.
Of course, right away!
Good. Bye.
Good morning, Thomas. Good morning, please come in.
Thank you.
This man was going to testify.
And he blew up his grave. Does it seem funny to you?
You have to admit, he's got style.
You put this man as president of the foundation and at the head of Brezovica.
And now you want to cut him off? Can he at least be a bit more discreet?
Discretion is not inherent in these people.
From the very beginning, since the war, this man does what we tell him to.
With him, we are the first in line for the privatization of this country.
And now you want to cut him off? Maybe he could be a little more discreet.
Discretion is not inherent in these people.
But obedience is. And I have a few obedient ones at hand.
Can they control him? No.
But they can persuade him that sometimes new ways are better than the old ones.
Seriously. Our friend is not a man you can play with.
Thomas, please go.
No, no. I understand everything.
I'll borrow from someone else. I know.
I know what the tax authorities do. Hold on.
Hello? Uroš Perić is calling.
Oh, my friend! What do I owe this honor to?
You told me you would come to Belgrade. Remember, you gave me a business card?
Yes, yes. And how is your sexy wife, huh?
You wouldn't dare to talk in front of her. I understand.
Something like that. Let's meet at 10.
Okay? And 300 euros will be enough, right? For you?
Okay. And you can hook up with some chick here,
with me, if you want. My treat.
Until next time. Let's go.
How did it go?
Okay.  What is this?
Petrite.  Why?
Provoked me.
I told you to be calm.
There you go... This is for you and your mom.
Like this... Where are you... Here you are! Here...
ANGELO DINI
Translated by AcePhil