Previously
Father, where are you going?
To the cemetery.
Can I come too?
Come.
He's in the operating room.
Fortunately, he was wearing a bulletproof vest.
Who did it?
I don't know.
Who would shoot a child?
The bullet severed Driton's tongue.
Why do you keep lying to me?
Where were you?
Do you think we don't see
how you're falling apart?
I'm sorry.
Dad, you need to pull yourself together.
Go ahead.
What do you want to hear?
The whole story.
We will block the entrances.
No one should dare to enter!
The situation is serious.
According to our information,
there are at least
15 armed individuals inside.
It's been a long time since we've seen each other.
Very long.
It was Bayram when you killed my father.
Our sources report
that Dardan Berisha has died,
but we still don't have definitive confirmation.
Where are you, Mima?
Huh? I heard you're unemployed now?
What are you playing at?
Come on, kids, greet your father!
Show some manners.
Hello, Dad!
Hello, children.
Let's go to the yard,
let's talk.
See how well-mannered Mima is?
When he comes as a guest,
he brings gifts.
Hired killer
Show your father how you kill them.
Go.
And you, show your plush toy. Go!
Come here.
And I have bad news for you.
Our mutual friend
has crossed the line.
Which is good news for me.
Let's go to the yard with you.
Let's have a talk.
Maybe, if you ask me nicely.
Please.
See, children, how
a kind word opens iron gates.
I say I am an iron gate, you understand?
Where are you?
For the last time, I'm dealing with you!
Understood?
Understood!
When I call - you answer!
You come where I say!
Is that clear?
Clear!
Hug Mima and say goodbye!
Good day.
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
Episode 9 YAGO
Why are you silent?
Isn't there someone to report
this maniac to the police?
Who is this guy?
Do you hear me? What am I asking you?
He's...
A man I owe money to.
Is there anyone in this world
you don't owe money to?
How can you let such a guy
break into your home and harass the children?
Are you normal?
I'll call the police!
Don't provoke him, Maria!
Both of you are insane!
I can't believe
what you've gotten us into!
I'm going to sleep at my father's.
I'm sorry.
I didn't come to bother you.
Please, just see something.
Come in.
Who is this guy?
When I call, you answer!
Clear?  Sure!
I don't know.
Luca, do you know this guy?
I'm going to see how Driton is.
Driton?
He's wounded, but he's alive.
Were they police?
I don't know...
They were... in uniforms.
I'm going to get the doctor.
Don't.
Why?
Don't tell anyone...
Not even Teuta.
Why?
He's involved...
Someone from our side.
Why do you think so?
I sense it. You need
to take me to Kosovo. Quickly.
Your uncle will get you out.
Don't worry...
He's asleep now.
Rest...
Let her go to her room.
Come on, go.
I've done my part.
It's time for you to gather your people
and leave.
Agim sends his regards.
Thank you.
He instructed you personally
to finish the job.
The hospital is full of his people,
just let me try something
and they'll kill me on the spot.
Now you're in charge.
Make sure we're alone.
I'm not in charge, Skender is.
Hashim...
I didn't come here to explain myself to you.
The boss said what he wants.
It has to happen tomorrow.
And my wife?
And the child?
We'll take care of them.
Until you finish the job.
What if I die?
Agim gave Besa
to take care of them.
Miss Fisher!
Good evening.
Excuse me, I didn't mean to frighten you.
Mister... Sokoli, I presume.
Exactly.
What do you want?
You probably know
what happened to Mr. Berisha.
If he, God forbid,
doesn't recover,
I think you'll need
a serious partner.
The privatization of Brezovica
is a big deal.
And this new partner...
it's you, I suppose?
I just wanted to show
my enthusiasm, that's all.
Think about my proposal.
I will think about it.
I'll find a way to contact you.
Please, don't hesitate.
This is my nephew's number
in Bosevo.
He's keeping our money.
I've booked a hotel,
everything is arranged.
We'll see each other in a few days.
It's time.
I have to go.
Two shots in Agani.
The killer seems to have escaped
through the window,
we found shoeprints.
Then he went to the sea,
where his accomplice was waiting.
Alright, we'll get back to that later.
Who found the body?
Agani's future wife.
Did you get her statements?
Of course, but she didn't tell us
anything useful.
She didn't see anything,
except the dead body.
And Agani's bodyguards?
We questioned them too, of course.
They didn't see anything.
They didn't see the faces,
but they saw two men in a boat
and shot at them.
We're done here.
Here, here. These bullet traces...
They were made by Agani's people,
shooting from there.
We found blood here, but...
we determined it's not from the accomplice
in the murder.
Alright. Didn't you... send it
to the laboratory?
Yes, of course. We sent everything.
The killed accomplice is Ivan Bilic.
Local tavern owner and drunkard.
So, Ivan stayed
in the boat,
the killer escaped through the stairs...
And here the traces are lost.
Open from the back!
Hello, hello!
This is the food. People in the hospital
are hungry, let him pass!
How is the boss?
Still sleeping.
But the doctor said he's fine.
Excellent.
Go, get some rest.
Now it's my turn.
We'll see you tonight.
Forgive me...
Be silent!
Nothing has changed
since the last time I was here.
From your smile, I can tell
it was romantic.
I'm not smiling at all, colleague.
Continue.
Ah, yes. That's why we're here. The owner
of the café, the late Ivan Bilic,
was a citizen
of the Republic of Croatia, but...
But?
But his childhood and youth,
he spent in Belgrade.
And why is that important?
It's important because...
Ana! Come, please.
Ana, tell your colleague
what you told me.
He was around 40 years old, judging
by the accent, a Serb from Belgrade.
Recently, more and more of them
are coming from there.
Handsome, tall.
Wore a denim jacket...
And I think he knew Ivan.
I heard this person
calling him some nickname.
What did he call him?
- Ivaylo-Pimpek.
Did you hear how
the other person was called?
Well, something like...
I didn't hear very clearly...
Something like... Tuki.
- What?
Tuki. At least that's what I heard.
Tuki. And that's like Pimpek, right?
- Yes, yes.
Yes, people from Belgrade have many nicknames.
Okay, and?
- Nothing,
I mean, I didn't hear...
the whole conversation, I was busy...
I heard something about the gymnasium.
- Where?
Well, in Belgrade. Ivan spent
his childhood there.
Alright, thank you Ana.
That's all, you're free.
Finally, we have a real
detective task, Inspector.
Let's find out which Serbian male name
rhymes with...
Thank you, colleague. Let's leave
the rhyming for another time, shall we?
Ah, yes... Yes.
Please provide me with all the information
about Ivan Bilic as soon as possible
and urgently send the samples for analysis.
And will you have time for dinner?
Colleague, I am a high-ranking officer!
I didn't hear you tonight.
I have to go.
A major's omelette is not to be refused!
Speak.
Where did he go?
Home?
Thank you for your hospitality.
Wait!
You know, I didn't
treat your mother well.
I know. I was there too.
I know you were.
That's why I'm talking to you.
Don't...
become like me.
I can't mess up like you.
I love all my relatives.
Dad, I really can't
play "Broken Telephone"!
Fine.
I don't know. I'll give it to you if she wants it.
It's dad.
- What?
I can't talk now.
Come on, bye!
Why?
Who shoots at children?
Who?
Huh?
Who? Who shoots at children?
Traitor!
Enough!
- Damn it!
Do you see those news reporters?
Break their cameras!
I'm listening!
Listening?
- The deadline I gave them,
expires in six hours.
But I won't comply.
I need your agreement.
- To shoot? To start a war?
With all the civilians
we have in the hospital?
Maybe you're not thinking straight, Kochi!
- Kochi.
Kochi...
- The alternative is to let
Dardan Berisha do
whatever he wants in Montenegro.
The man on his deathbed?
- 21 people with automatic weapons!
The infiltration will prevent a serious
criminal act.
This is our only chance.
- We're not Russians, Kochi.
We're not 300 million to
attack, kill, and terrorize.
and the flea bit the bear.
I will personally lead the operation.
I guarantee the lives of the patients...
Enough, that's sufficient, Koçi.
We have never messed up
a situation like yours.
Communists ruled us for 50 years,
half of Montenegro,
brought us to begging with a stick.
And now, the old song with a new voice.
I won't send my people inside,
to become a laughingstock.
The life of even one person
is more valuable to me than all praises
from Lyon and Brussels and...
Chief, don't move!
The wheelchair...
Please don't move.
They'll reopen your wounds.
The wheelchair.
Don't. He needs to see... to hear.
Who ordered Dardan's murder?
Who?
Your brother-in-law.
Your brother-in-law!
He still doesn't move.
Tonight, I'll tell her everything.
Go home. Listen to me,
go home while you still have someone.
I just spoke with the Minister
of Internal Affairs personally.
They are preparing an emergency risk analysis.
We'll learn his decision soon.
That's good.
The moment they stormed
a public institution armed
with rifles, they defined themselves
as terrorists.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Whatever the Minister decides,
please don't take matters into your own hands.
Don't worry.
That's my job.
Until soon.
What if he wakes up
while he's in the coffin?
No, they gave him a sedative.
He'll wake up in Kosovo.
Easy... like this...
It's not so bad here.
You come with me. We'll go upstairs
to wait for that dog.
Really?
Okay.
Looks like they got permission
to storm.
Don't worry, everything will be fine!
I've got everything under control.
Those who shot Dardan
were wearing police uniforms.
How do we know it's not one of them?
Trust me, they're my concern.
Special forces are coming.
What are we going to do?
We'll wait. We'll wait!
Listen. The Minister said yes.
Get your people ready.
Where are you going?
I'm driving two corpses to Podgorica.
They'll be buried tomorrow.
Open from the back!
Open the coffin!
Bad luck will catch up with me!
Open it!
You open it, I don't dare.
Neighbor, don't open that, please.
Neighbor, don't open this one,
I beg you.
To everyone! Take positions
to start the operation.
Ready.
This is my uncle.
He died of skin cancer.
His whole body decayed.
Open the other one.
A young kid, a sympathizer.
Attack!
Let's go, run!
Attack! Attack!
You all know your job.
Find Dardan!
Forward!
Kneel! Kneel! Down!
Down! Down!
Everyone down!
Scander...
Good day, Inspector Koçi.
What's happening here?
Nothing.
We waited for you to come
so we could go home.
Where's your nephew?
He went out to smoke a cigarette.
There's no one.
What's this?
What is all this nonsense?
Where is Dardan?
Maybe he got better and went home.
You attacked the hospital,
took hostages.
Do you think you'll get away with it?
Well, arrest us then.
But I don't see
how that will bring back your father.
Let's run away from here.
Come on, quickly!
We're leaving.
Spasoje...
Hello! Koçi...
Interpol can't solve everything!
This is Montenegro, legend.
Follow me!
REPUBLIC OF KOSOVO
Yes, I'm here.
Yes, I understand.
Yes, no problem.
Hello?
Hello, little sister. How are you?
Alive, but I'd be better off dead.
Don't say that. Be strong.
How is Agime, how? Tell me how,
because I no longer know how to be strong?
What kind of person would shoot at children?
Does he have a soul, a conscience?
How does he walk on this earth?
How, brother?
What kind of person is this?
Currently, there's no connection
with this number...
Uroš?
We need to talk.
Translated by AcePhil