Previously:
Come on, kids, greet your dad!
Show some manners.
Let's talk in the yard.
This is the last time I'm dealing with you!
Clear?  Sure.
Agim sends his regards. He personally ordered you
to finish the job.
Forgive me...
Who is this guy?
I don't know.
Go home.
Who was it?
Your brother-in-law!
We got approval from the minister.
Prepare the people.
To everyone! Take positions
for the operation.
Find Dardan!
Good day, Inspector Koci.
Where is Dardan?
I'm taking two corpses to Podgorica.
They'll be buried tomorrow.
Come on, run.
Run away from here.
Save yourself!
What kind of person would shoot at children?
Does he have a soul, a conscience?
What kind of person is this?
And where is Dardan Berisha now?
Perhaps we would have
this information,
if the chief prosecutor of Montenegro
had not refused this morning
to arrest Skender Berisha and his people
and bring charges against them.
We can't press them constantly, Koci.
Forget about it and try
to find Dardan Berisha.
That's why I'm here.
Skender remains free.
See, I've already checked half
of the Belgrade high schools for this guy
and nothing, but something else very important
came to my mind.
For example, what happened
that Hashim disappeared so suddenly?
This could mean...
Keep searching.
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
Episode 10 KINSMEN
Yes.
We sent you the documents via email.
Everything is verified.
My source from the privatization agency
confirmed it.
So, war?
Blood is already being shed. The murder
in Rovin is definitely related to this.
Agani was a decoy for Agim.
Only Dardan has a motive. He found out
that this one is a candidate for the auction.
Where did he find out?
He speaks Serbian.
The documents were submitted
48 hours before the murder.
My only person had access
to this information, and he's clean.
What about the German?
The one who leads the fund.
Well, we need to check him.
Avdi. See what you can dig up.
Okay.
The laboratory analysis from Lyon
has arrived.
And?
The DNA sample from Rovin completely
matches the other DNA samples.
So, we have the killer.
We just need to find out who he is.
Divna... the veins.
The veins!
Is this some new method?
Yes, it is. The latest.
To get enlarged veins
while I search through all the archives.
The newcomers who came here
are now against the government.
Good thing someone
remembered to dig into...
And was this some specialized
opposition high school?
Oh, no. There were also people from the authorities.
All generations have passed through here
since 1858.
I won't keep you any longer,
I'll return the key to the director.
Thank you.
- Some of the diaries,
have long been destroyed.
Thanks to the former authorities.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
What wouldn't I give to soak
apricots in the sea once again.
Damn the sea!
True, now you enjoy
killing people.
Maria has gone crazy.
I told her everything.
Mare!
Mare! Get up, Mare!
What are you doing here?
Don't overdo it with those pills,
they'll fry your brain.
Leave, or I'll...
I'll call the police!
Really?
And what, you'll tell them everything?
And do you gnash your teeth when
you have to kill someone?
Are you deaf?
I told everything to Maria.
And?
Now she acts like everything is fine
in front of the kids.
But I know we...
But I know we are separated.
It's strange, you tell your wife
that you kill people,
and she gets mad at you.
Oops! Good day, Ivan Bilich!
Won't someone sing for you?
Like Maria, for example? No.
I reached an agreement with Uros to tell you.
Everything.
I believe that in a marriage
there should be no secrets.
Marriage is a sacred union. You'll
forgive me, but I'm old-fashioned.
Did he tell you? What did he say?
It would be tough, brother.
You come home one evening,
after some murder, and your wife comes
and says, "Honey, I called the police!"
Wait, what will you do?
Will you clean her?
He told me he owes money to someone.
If it's you, we'll settle!
- No, look, there's no need...
The two of us will handle it.
All day I call him, and he
doesn't answer. Where is he?
At his friend's.
- At the one dying of cancer?
Well, then I have to hurry,
catch him while he's still alive.
Greetings to the kids.
I fell in love with the boy...
And I don't miss the girl.
Goodbye, Mare!
Where is Petrit?
- He's not here, he's in the bathroom.
I don't have time for this. Do you know
who was Ivan Bilich's classmate?
Who?
Uros! Uros Perich.
There's no chance he's the killer!
He probably went to Rovinj
because of some chick.
That's quite manly logic.
Petrit, please! Come on, believe me.
Just trust me.
We need to check Perich.
Mr. Perich, thank you
for coming.
I didn't have much choice.
- Actually, you had no choice.
Okay. Mr. Perich, when was the last time
you were in Croatia?
Am I suspected of something?
- No, no.
Because if I am, I would like
to talk to my lawyer.
You don't need a lawyer,
we're just talking.
You don't need a lawyer
to answer us, right?
Well, tell me about Croatia...
And why do you want to know?
- Answer.
Well, I was in Croatia...
6 months ago.
Mr. Perić, do you know Ivan Bilić?
- No.
Are you sure?
- Yes.
Actually... that was the name
of a classmate of mine from high school.
Doesn't he still have that name?
- Most likely he still does.
Unless he took his wife's last name.
- I haven't seen him since 1991. He moved to Croatia back then.
Ivan Bilić was killed
7 days ago in Rovinj.
We think the same person who killed
Mehmet Agani killed him.
Ivan Bilić was your friend?
- Ivan and I went to school together,
We hoped that you could help us
with the investigation.
And who is Ahmet Agani?
- Mehmet Agani.
Mehmet.
- Croatian businessman.
Associate of Agim Sokoli, the eccentric
friend of your friend Dardan Berisha.
You very well know that
Dardan Berisha is not my friend.
And Ivan was your friend?
- Ivan and I studied together,
I told you, we haven't seen each other
in a hundred years
and it can't be said
that he was my friend.
Mr. Perić, what were you doing
in Rovinj ten days ago?
I haven't been to Rovinj in 10 years.
Yet you were seen in Rovinj
ten days ago with the murdered man in his café.
Why are you talking nonsense?
I haven't been to Rovinj,
I haven't seen Ivan,
and now if you please,
either let me go,
or let me call my lawyer.
Call your lawyer.
No connection.
- This is a protected building of the Ministry of Interior.
Alright, let me make a call
from the landline.
Visitors are not allowed
to use the official phone.
In that case... goodbye.
Inspector Mirko Sandić.
- What do you want from me?
I want you to sit.
- I won't sit, I want to leave!
Uroš... sit.
Are we on a first-name basis?
Now we're best friends.
You see... Dukić and I
bet on something.
Maybe you can help us?
She thinks somehow you're involved
in the murder of Ivan Bilić.
And I think you're not
capable of that.
Tell us, who's right?
You.
- Who?
You're right.
I was in Rovinj 7 days ago
and met Ivan.
But in no way
am I involved in his murder.
What were you doing there?
There's a woman there,
who's married.
There you go!
I suppose your wife
is not aware?
Of course she's not aware.
- And you don't want her to find out?
In that case, tell us everything
about your meeting with Ivan.
There's not much to tell.
I told my wife I was leaving...
At work.
Actually, I went to Rovin.
And there...
I accidentally met Ivan.
- Yes, and?
And I was glad we saw each other.
Due to circumstances.
- Yes.
And that's it, I think.
Nothing...
We had coffee, and that's it. I'm not...
- Excuse me, Mr. Perich,
where did you stay while in Rovin?
I think that goes without saying.
You don't want to tell us who she is?
- Please don't.
I understand.
Okay. Now we've clarified some things.
Can I leave?
- If you ask me, yes.
Mr. Perich, can I
ask for a little more help?
If you'd be so kind
as to provide a DNA sample for analysis.
Why?
- It's just a formality.
We just want to exclude you
as a suspect
in the murder of Ivan Bilich. You know,
the Croatian police insist on that.
This is an order
from the Croatian prosecutor.
I want a lawyer immediately!
In that case, we'll detain you
for 72 hours and report you
to the chief prosecutor.
- What will you report me for?
Complicity in the murder
of Ivan Bilich.
What murder?
What murder, damn it?
I have nothing to do with these murders!
In that case, give us a sample
and you're free.
Can I leave now?
- Of course, go ahead.
Unlike Inspector Kocic,
I am completely sure
that you are capable of such a thing.
Female intuition, I suppose?
Many murderers are family people.
- Goodbye.
Hello?
Why did you call me?
Do you remember the one who comes to you?
The one from the video clip?
This crazy one, this...
The one who harasses people?
What do you have to do with him?
Well, I work for him.
What do you work?
See, your father has really stepped on the line.
Where is he going?
- Let me go!
They'll fuck us up,
if they see us together, clear?
I don't care! Let me go!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
VILLAGE IN KOSOVO
Open up!
Does it hurt?
How about now?
Okay.
Shall we try something else?
Try saying... Driton.
Driton.
Okay.
Try saying...
Rruga (street).
Rru-ga.
Okay. Let's try
to say nona (mother).
No-na.
Come on, once more.
Just once more, come on.
No-na.
Everything's fine.
It's not good.
The wound is healing well,
but the tongue is damaged.
And I'm afraid he won't be able
to speak anymore.
Never?
I'm sorry to have to tell you this,
but I want to be honest.
The bullet has taken off
a large part of his tongue.
Thank you.
Madam.
Did Agim know
that Driton would be in the car?
I don't think so.
If he knew, he wouldn't have ordered
to shoot the child.
But Hashim saw him.
He saw him.
- The bloodsucker will get him!
Don't do that, he's your brother.
This is between me and Agim.
You and the children shouldn't become
victims of our feud.
Listen!
Take the children and get out of here.
Go to a safe place.
I'll take care of it.
Hello?
Okay.
I'm coming.
- What's happening?
I have to go to Kosovo.
Come on, drive.
Take the keys.
My car is at Gazela.
Come on, let's go.
Did your friend tell you
he's coming home?
Which friend?
- Who do you think?
Mima.
- What, did Mima come home?
Yes.
- Why didn't he tell me?
Well, now I'm telling you.
And?
- Nothing. He's asking what you told me.
- Well, I didn't tell him anything!
He doesn't know anything.
What happened at the police?
They took a DNA sample for analysis.
Why?
- They know I've been to Rovin.
I lied to them that I have a lover there.
And now what?
I don't know what now.
Come on.
- Come on.
Call me.
- Everything will be fine.
Goodbye.
- Well, goodbye.
What have you been doing at home today?
Huh?
- What did I sing?
Listen, you psychopath! If you come home
again, I'll kill you!
What did he sing, huh?
- If I had sung, I wouldn't be here!
They know I've been to Rovin and
they took a DNA sample from me.
Damn you!
How will I travel?
This is Rize.
Hey, hey!
The phone.
Damn you...
When I tell you to be quiet,
is it clear!
Don't shout! Don't shout!
Help!
Help! No!
- Hold her! Hold her hands!
Wait, wait!
Don't shout!
Hello, hey!
Shut up, mom!
Hello there!
I can't see! I can't see!
Move your hand!
You motherf***er! I'll blow you up!
I'll tear you apart!
Come on, bring it on!
This is going on the internet
if I see you with Luka again!
And don't call again!
Get him inside.
Good night, sweetheart!
Hey! How are you?
What's up?
Can I come in?
What?
I might be paranoid,
but the results from Lyon arrived.
And what do they say?
All the samples match
the one we took from Uroš Perić.
Just give me a minute.
Go call your sister, please.
Let's eat.
Are you feeling okay?
See you...
What?
Tell mom I'm still asleep.
Still asleep.
Una?
Police!
Don't run!
Get inside! Inside!
See you!
Check upstairs!
Where is my daughter?
Lie down!
Stay with the little one!
Good day, Mr. Petrović.
Mrs. Perić.
Inspector Koçi, the way
you arrested my client is unacceptable.
Are we going to discuss
police powers, or will we get to the point?
I'm listening.
Interrogation of Maria Perić, related to the criminal case
in which her husband, Uroš Perić,
is a suspect.
The interrogation will be conducted by Inspector Petrit Koçi
and Divna Dukić from Interpol,
in the presence of
lawyer Pavel Petrović.
Mrs. Perić, do you know
where your husband is right now?
I don't know, I already told you.
When did you last see him?
Yesterday morning.
And didn't he tell you where he was going?
He didn't tell me, no. We haven't been
talking much in the last two months.
So, no.
Since the incident?
Exactly, yes.
Look... it's hard for me
to believe this.
Look... I don't care
if you believe me or not.
Say whatever you have to say,
arrest me or let me go!
Maria...
Don't mess with me, Pavel! Let me go!
Will you tell me why
my client was arrested,
what evidence you have against her?
Of course, we arrested her
because we suspect she was
an accomplice to her husband, Uroš Perić,
in several serious criminal
offenses.
Including murders,
infliction of serious bodily harm,
illegal possession of weapons,
and intentional
misleading
investigating authorities.
Murders? Uroš?
In a span of a few months,
several murders happened
related to Dardan Berisha.
Your client's husband is involved.
DNA analysis shows he's been
at all the crime scenes.
Inspector Kocic,
you know very well
that DNA analysis alone
is not sufficient evidence.
It's sufficient
to issue an Interpol Red Notice for Uros.
I've known your client's husband
for over 30 years.
I'm completely sure
he's not capable of...
Mr. Petrovic, thank you
for your personal opinion, but please,
let your client tell us
what her husband is capable of!
You invaded my house.
You arrested me,
and now you're telling me my husband
is a mass murderer? Are you normal?
Maria...
Mrs. Peric...
- What?!
Mrs. Peric,
once we catch Uros, he'll never
get out again.
And pray to God it happens.
Because the criminals
he kills for will eliminate him
at the first opportunity.
You have two options. Either end up
in jail with your husband
and risk your children's lives,
or help us find Uros.
In that case, I promise you,
we'll do everything we can
to get you into the
witness protection program.
Show the pictures, please.
Ulcin.
Belgrade.
Rovin.
Can you leave us alone
for a few minutes?
Of course.
Maria...
- What?
If you know anything about this,
now's the time to tell me.
I don't know anything. How would I know?
What could I know about it?
Okay.
Whatever happens, I'll get you out.
What have you decided?
My client wants to state that
she has no connection to the events
you mentioned. And that she has
no information about her husband.
Alright.
- Alright.
In that case, can we go?
- You can.
The lady will stay here overnight.
- Why?
- Just taking advantage of the law.
What are you doing? Completely...
- Okay, Pavle...
Why are you doing this?
- Pavle, there's no problem. Okay.
Everything's fine.
And the children? Should I call Bozo?
Don't call Bozo, please.
Can you stay with them tonight?
No problem.
- Thank you, Pavle.
Don't mention it.
Last calls:
Luka
Translated by AcePhil