Previously
Trust me.
Spill my blood, and you'll get yours.
You'll kill five people for me.
He's broken. - Luka.
Offered to buy me another. - Some stranger will buy you a phone?
He's not a stranger; Dad knows him. - Me?
Yes. And someone named Mima sends regards to you.
Who's Mima? - Listen to me.
If you have any problems, come to me!
Nice, we don't need you. We'll deal with the little one.
Carefully. With knives, with cocks, and you'll watch.
Kisses.
Get lost, I can't stand you! Such a bitch!
A few days ago, Dardan Berisha ordered an autopsy of his daughter.
I have nothing to do with it.
Look, I believe you. But will Dardan believe you?
Our business is settled.
There's only one big thing left to settle.
Don't stick your nose in my affairs!
Good evening, Mr. Bey. Mr. Berisha wants to talk to you.
I'll miss my flight. - We'll take you to the airport.
So... you're David?
Yes, I am.
Besi spoke a lot about you.
Excuse me; you're probably wondering why I wanted to see you.
It's complicated. You're the last person who saw my daughter alive.
Her last conversation was with you.
What did she say? - Excuse me?
What were her last words?
That she's fed up with the beach. And she wants to go somewhere else.
Of course. You should've listened to her.
That's how it was with all the men in her life. With me, with her brother.
She is greatly missed.
At one point, I thought you were responsible for Bessiana's death.
I almost believed you made her drink or take drugs and then left her to drive.
So, I arranged an autopsy for Bessiana.
And do you know what they found?
Nothing.
I was ready to tear your heart out with my bare hands.
And now it seems I owe you an apology.
I was supposed to apologize.
Now it looks like I owe you an apology.
You thought the same as any father. - That's right.
Thank you. Thank you for sharing Bessiana's last moment with me.
Wishing you a pleasant flight.
David...
Did you love her?
Yes.
Call Belgrade.
Tell them to reactivate the driver.
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
Episode 5 BURN
Hello, sweetheart!
You're very sexy when you're silent.
Why him?
As you're curious, you're even sexier.
How's the company? - Super.
Wait, wait. Turn it off.
Carrier of medicines.
Pharma Trans.
You have a debt of 720,000 to the bank.
How do you know that? - I know everything.
With one click, I can solve your problem and transfer the money.
I don't need your help. - Don't say that; you have a beautiful wife.
And beautiful women run away when companies go bankrupt.
Your daughter is a sweetheart. Born to be fucked by cocks.
Excuse me, but I'd fuck her out of her mind.
If you touch me again, I'll rip your head off!
Stay there before it gets dark.
David left the hotel.
Agim's people? - Yes, from his people.
On our territory?
On our territory, and with goods!
Call Enver.
And be careful. Don't kill them.
The phone.
Get out!
Hey! Do you want me to help you?
Come on, please. Give.
You need a gentle touch, not a man's paw.
And who are you dressing up for?
I'm dressing up for Natasha. We're going out.
Where are you going? Should I come pick you up?
Mind your own business.
No need to come, I'll take the bus back.
No. You'll come back by taxi.
Sure, come on. Thanks.
Please, I don't want everyone to drive you home.
Not everyone will drive me home.
Bye. Bye. Have a good time.
Thank you.
Is this what you've lost?
Yes, it is.
Come in.
I haven't used this perfume in a hundred years.
It was with this perfume, that night at the concert. When we met.
How could you not forget it? I haven't.
Thank you. And...
There's more.
This.
If I missed the mark, I can return it immediately.
It's not about that...
Better return it.
What's wrong? You're tickling me.
No, wait. What?
I need to quickly stop by Pavel's. Now?
Yes, right away.  Why?
To get some money. What money?
For the loan. I asked him for a loan. Why ask Pavel again?
Who else? We can borrow from our own, I don't know!
No, no. I've already solved the problem. Wait for me, please. I won't be long.
Well... I have to go. Come on.
Are you going now? Yes, I'm going now.
Unknown number: Same place at 6:30 PM.
Hello. Hello.
You look older. And you look younger.
Come in. Thank you.
Tell me, what will you drink?
Rosé spritzer.
Nice restaurant you have.
Thank you. Where did you get it?
From my father.
Come in.
What's this?
What I promised you.
And what did I say?
You'll come out very persistent.
What can I do, that's how I am.
Come in.
Alright.
What's wrong? What's the problem?
I'm not like that.
Everyone is like that. It's a matter of motivation.!
Do you remember the case of the abducted child
with Dr. Todorovich, a few years ago?
You read about it, it was in all the newspapers.
They say they still haven't found the child.
They're lying. They found him.
Dr. Todorovich found him personally.
Every week, I sent him a piece of it.
So he could put it back together.
I returned his son.
Come on. Finish your job.
MARIA
Baby, are you still awake?
Are you ready to go? Baby?
Mother...
Get up, you fucking bitch!
Wake up, you sleepy cunt!
Who are you, huh?
I didn't order room service, get lost!
When you kill for the first time, you vomit.
The second time is easier. You can even have an espresso.
The third time, you start to like it.
Soon you'll understand.
Drink? I'm messed up.
Me too. Where are we going?
Let's go home. Come on again.
Where are we going?
Lead the way.
And what would you do? What would I do?
I would go up to the balcony and that's it.
I would... I'm late, sorry.
Ah, here's the third for the cards.
No, I think you're wrong.
You're wrong again. He didn't come to play cards.
He doesn't care to see his friends.
Something else matters to him.
Do you have something to drink?
Just let me clear this. Sorry. You're fine.
And? Now is the time to say "thank you."
What is this?
Thank you, brother! I don't know, how many times you saved me. You're great!
Thank you. Thank you.
So, I have cytostatics, but they're not that great.
Whiskey, homemade brandy. Give the homemade to the homebodies.
Do you remember that summer, the last one before the war?
At the international camp in Rovin, we were still kids.
The whole world was at our feet And then, everything went to hell.
16 years old, at the peak of life. Madness, complete madness.
Remember? I do.
Alright, come on...
Come on, those two girls over there.
I don't know. Come on, check them out carefully.
I can't. Watch them.
Tequila... - Alright.
Watch now, add soda, fill the glass. Watch now!
Boom-boom. What were you drinking in high school?
Come on again. Come...
Come on, see this. What's the boy doing?
Kahlúa... And now gently and carefully pour Baileys on top.
So that it stays on top, like foam, floating.
Baby Guinness. Like a little beer. - Bravo.
Excellent for a mother. - Sorry, but I'm a single mother
and I need to be informed. And you know nothing.
I'm used to brandy.
I have nothing against brandy, as long as it doesn't bother you later.
But there are so many drinks, one has to try different things.
I don't want to mix brandy with anything else, if it's not a problem.
Should it be a problem? All problems around you.
We've come out for a drink, to relax.
A person can't just work, Koči.
So you want to talk about me. - If you want to talk about me.
I'm a single mother, my life is an inexhaustible topic.
Are you okay? I mean...
Is everything in order? - Everything is absolutely, perfectly...
...foolishness. Which you probably have no way of knowing.
What?
And you avoid such things too.
Well, if I have a story too? - Is it sad?
I don't know. I'll tell you, and you'll decide.
I'm listening.
I had a friend who studied in Belgrade.
He fell in love with... - a girl from a respected Belgrade family.
Everything was great until his intentions became serious.
Everything fell apart when they broke up.
What happened? - They broke up, and that was it.
Why? - Because, my friend
wasn't Serbian enough.
I'm sorry. - For what?
I'm not sorry. I mean...
The important thing is that my friend is better now.
He doesn't think about it anymore. Now he thinks about other things.
Like what?
About the wounds on the body of the late Italian journalist.
About the caliber of the weapon used, about the style of elimination.
I want you to find me all the information
on professional mafia killings in the past year.
I'll do it right away.
Finish your drink. You still have more.
For the road. - Alright.
You're going home. - Hey!
I don't want to go home.
Where do you want to go?
Let me drive you home.
Welcome.
This place seems familiar to me.
And I need something unfamiliar.
Good night and sweet dreams.
Good night.
And don't forget your bag.
I've got my bag.
Bye.
Good night.
Dad? Yes?
Are you okay? Yes, yes.
Are you sure? Yes.
Come and open the door for me, please.
What's wrong with you? I feel nauseous.
Do you need anything? No. Are you sure?
Yes. Are you sure?
Come on, go to bed. Okay.
Good night.
OHRID
Quiet! Quiet! Speak! Where is the drugs? Where?
In the trunk... In the trunk.
Quiet... Shut your mouth, or I'll clean you up!
You seem smarter to me, so I'm talking to you...
Be silent. Silent!
Come on... quickly!
Put her inside.
Give my regards to Agim.
Did you take everything you need?
Inspector Koci. General Premovic.
Inspector Dukic. Jovic.
What are you doing here?
I was called by the British Embassy.
You understand that this is also the work of Dardan Berisha?
Possible.
I would like you to join us.
How nice of you! Jovic?
The girl who was with him found his body in the morning.
The door was locked,
and the card - a key was placed in the electricity socket.
So we assume the Englishman knew the killer.
The attacker shot on the move.
The Englishman ran towards the bathroom.
One bullet is in the pillow, and two more in the picture on the wall.
There's another one in the door frame safe. All the rest are in him.
Very strange! What's strange?
There are too many bullets.
The attacker missed a lot of shots from close range.
He acted like an amateur.
Or he got scared. Or he wanted to look that way.
I received some video. Probably from the cameras.
Play it.
This is not going well!
Bad news from Macedonia.
Dardan's people intercepted the Dauti brothers in Ohrid.
They took 50 kilograms from them.
Well done. Did they beat them?
They wounded one in the leg. Sending you greetings.
Well done. It's time for you to go to Montenegro.
Get ready. We're paying a visit.
Hey! What are you preparing?
Let me see! What?
Do you know how scared Viden got when he saw your bruises? Show me!
He promised me that they won't bother us anymore, right?
You're wrong. This has nothing to do with the mafia.
I argued with some people in the traffic jam, and they beat me up.
Urose, I'm not a fool! Don't mutter to me and don't lie to me!
You will ruin everything we have.
You're right. No, don't...
No, really. I shouldn't have lied to you.
I just didn't want to worry you. Urose...
I didn't want you to worry. Do you understand?
You look so sexy with that board!
Are the kids here? I don't know, they should be at school.
Let's see.
Good day, Good day, Mrs. Peric.
Inspectors Petrit Koci and Divna Dukic from Interpol.
Is your husband at home?
Translated by AcePhil