Previously
Good day.
Good day, Mrs. Perich.
Is your husband at home?
People like Berisha,
eliminate entire families,
without blinking an eye.
I heard you want to get involved
in a legal business?
Today we received the documents
from another participant.
From a Croatian company
named "Adria Nord".
Leave your phone. The one in the package
has a Bosnian ID.
Tell your wife
that you're going to Banja Luka.
Your husband parked his car
in the "Delta City" parking lot,
he went inside and hasn't
come out since. The car is still there.
Do you know where he is?
What are you doing with the little one?
Nothing.
Fuck her?
No.
If I see you with her again,
I'll kill her!
ROVIN
What are you doing here?
You're my wife.
Don't you know you have obligations?
You do.
Don't touch me!
Do I have obligations, right?
Translated by AcePhil
BESA
Love...
Episode 6 DOUBT
Get ready!
We're going to Kosovo.
To Kosovo?
Everything is here.
Children go to school here.
We have no choice. It's become dangerous here.
For the whole family.
Besiana's grave is here.
We'll move her there.
We'll move everything. Pack your bags!
Hello, love?
Hey!
What's happening?
I've been in meetings all day.
And how is it going?
What can I tell you?
He's offering me to become
his main representative in Serbia.
And you know how it is with customs.
Yes.
And when are you coming back?
It should be tomorrow morning.
I have another meeting in the afternoon,
and tonight I'm invited for lamb.
I can't refuse.
Okay.
Which hotel did you say you were staying at?
Maria, I have to go to a meeting at OUME.
What did he say?
Come on, we'll talk later. Bye.
Did something happen to dad?
Yes.
Come on, mom, he'll be okay.
The girl he killed was my age.
How can he not go crazy?
We're leaving in three days.
The four of us are leaving and
another ten people that Hashim will choose.
First, we'll stay at Skender's house.
And then we'll see.
Any questions?
Can I stay here?
To command those who remain?
Why?
My wife is pregnant...
Again?  What can you do?
And she might be pregnant.
I need everyone.
Anyone who wants can
take their family. Hashim...
It's not easy for him...
Neither does he have a wife, nor does he care.
I care.
You'll become a great lover...
That's right. I'm not a count like you.
Hashim, one more thing...
When did you last have sex?
Last year, I had a little encounter...
But it's as if I haven't.
He's my fucker!
In three days, everything has to be ready.
Everything has to continue,
as if we're still here.
The business here will be run
by the fat Riza.
Understood?
Blazo, every time you look at me
as if you want to kill me on the spot!
If I didn't kill you when you killed
my son-in-law and brought my niece
for me to take care of,
it means I won't now.
I saved her life, Blazo!
- That's why I let you live!
And staining our honor,
sooner or later, it will come back to you.
Maybe.
But not from you.
- Not from me. I gave you my word.
And I gave you a grandson!
Yes, he gave me a grandson!
Ask him.
He might let you stay here.
I already asked him.
Hashim doesn't ask for a living,
he prays.
Yes.
You've set aside enough money
for a rainy day.
You knew that these days would come.
Here they are.
It's time to run.
Where will we run?
Where won't Dardan find us?
It would have been better if he had killed me,
as he ordered you!
Please, don't leave!
I'll die without you!
I have no choice.
I'll prepare something for you to eat.
What would you like?
- Double espresso and Coca-Cola.
Of course.
Can I have a double espresso
and Coca-Cola?
Here you go.
- Thank you.
I didn't order wine, no.
Uki-Tuki?
Oh, man...
Now you have to say Ivek-Pimpek!
Ivan.
- Oh, brother...
Ivan!
- Where are you, man?
Where are you going, my Uki?
Uki-Tuki!
I can't believe it.
- What brings you here?
Sit.
- It's a long story.
Well, if it's long, start.
Take your time...
Come on!
- Ah, no, no, no
Don't be early for me!
- Come on, start. Let me hear you.
And you, what are you doing here?
- Well, I live here.
Wait, weren't you in Zagreb?
I got married, got divorced...
My wife took the apartment...
My second wife was a tavern keeper.
And she deceived me.
And I bought this trap from her.
That's how my luck was!
Such was my fate!
And you? Tell me!
- Well...
I'm here because of a girl.
- Oh!
If my wife finds out, she'll kill me.
Damn it! Do you know, I've always envied you.
For the pieces. I mean,
for the girls. Always.
Belgrade girls, huh?
You know...
I haven't been there
since we finished high school.
Damn. What's there to do?
Man...
I'll never forget
how you saved me back then.
When the nationalists were beating me.
- I didn't save you...
On the contrary.
- You're exaggerating, it was nothing.
- They wouldn't have killed you.
No, they would just beat me up.
Just that they buried me in concrete
and cursed my Croatian mother!
Because I wouldn't take off
the Partizan shirt from underneath.
How could I take it off when
I had a Dinamo shirt underneath?
If I knew that, I would never
have jumped them. Luckily, I didn't know.
Hey, little one!
Bring another pitcher.
Please, come on.
Man, everyone stood and watched,
the whole school.
And out of everyone, only you jumped
to save me.
Uki, that's unforgettable. Even after
a concussion.
Yes, that's right. You saved my life, Uki.
- It's not like that, you're exaggerating.
Life!
- Yes, indeed.
Hey, you know how glad I am
to meet you!
We should celebrate tonight.
- The girl is waiting for me, I can't.
Okay, then tomorrow, but first
I'll take you to lunch,
and then we'll sit down
and have a drink, okay? Please.
Which hotel are you staying at?
Ivek-Pimpek. Why do you ask so much?
Excuse me. And where is your girl?
There she is.
Aim high, damn it.
Come on.
Come on, I'll take you by boat.
- How? There's no...
Come on, let's go...
- Don't say a word!
Come on!
- There's a boat every 15 minutes...
We won't argue now.
- No need, really...
Let's go!
- Wait, I'll pay the bill...
No, no, no! I'll handle it.
Write it on me!
Please, brother! Uki.
- Don't do this.
The money of my fellow student
doesn't matter here!
No need, I have a reservation...
- We're leaving, let's go!
No need for you to drive me...
- We're leaving.
Here, take it.
- Look at that guy with the BMW!
Where?
Take the phone.
- What?
We'll see each other tomorrow, right?
- Where are you going, hello?
"This is him."
Well, hello.
Where are you in such a hurry?
Will you tell me who arranged you like this?
Ah, Luka? I won't be mad,
if it's because of some girl.
Luka?
What's up?
Una, we can't see each other anymore.
What?
Are you kidding?
I'm not kidding.
And why?
- I can't explain it to you.
What can't you explain to me?
Don't call me anymore and
drag me into the café, okay?
Luka, huh?
So what? He fooled me and dumped me?
- I fooled you, yes. So what?
LION
INTERPOL
This is from Mr. Berisha's lawyer,
Adnan Braha.
There are some quite serious
accusations against you.
Mr. Braha claims that when taking
DNA samples,
you exceeded your authority
and unlawfully arrested his client.
Yes. Mr. Braha is a criminal.
As well as his clients.
- Allow me to finish, miss.
He also claims that instead of taking
samples from his clients,
you organized an operation
to arrest them.
And thus you have threatened the lives not only
of Mr. Berisha and his associates,
but also of his son, who is still a child.
That "child" pulled a gun
against the police.
Is it true that you used offensive
words for Mr. Berisha's daughter,
which almost led to
physical confrontation?
Yes, it is true.
I wanted to provoke him
to do something,
for which I could arrest him.
While he is free,
the whole region will sink into chaos,
so...
This provocation may
cost us dearly.
Berisha's lawyer will probably
file a complaint with Interpol
and seek a huge compensation.
And you know,
that this will automatically lead
to your removal.
Then remove me.
Please?
- If he leaves, I leave too.
Yes. Get rid of us.
But with this move, you will admit
that they are unbeatable.
Mr. Kochi...
- Yes?
Consider this as a final warning.
Thank you,
for this last chance.
Hello, sister. How are you?!
I want to ask you something.
Tell me!
Dardan ordered everyone to move
to Kosovo. I don't want to live there.
Haven't you discussed it?
We did, but it's like
talking to a wall.
Alright. I'll try
to talk to him.
And you can come
to me for the weekend.
I'll send a plane to pick you up.
Alright, I'll come.
If he allows...
Is he treating you roughly?
No, he's not rough with me.
You know, if it weren't for the kids,
I would have escaped in a heartbeat.
Don't talk like that. He's your husband.
Come to me for the weekend.
I'll convince him to let you go.
Alright.
Let's go.
I talked to Agim.
He invited us with the kids
to go to him for the weekend.
Good.
Are we going now?
Go.
You need to go, be
with your family for a bit.
But the kids stay here.
Why?
Because I say so.
Agim, the boss...
He's heard a lot of good things about you.
He's offering you a job.
If he knows everything about me,
then he knows I'm not a traitor.
Why like this, man?
And as for betrayal...
Let me tell you...
You betrayed Dardan that night,
when you didn't follow his order.
And saved this one's life.
Where did you learn about her?
Kill us both.
Just don't touch my niece.
Spare my grandson.
Please.
Should I kill you?
Why should I kill you?
Regain your honor, kill yourself.
Don't squeal at me like a pussy.
See, I'm talking to a man.
Oh, Hashim, Hashim...
I had my people follow you.
They told me you were sneaking
into the house of some Montenegrin.
And I thought: "What's going on?"
Why do you go there?
Are you perhaps a fag?
Are you fags?
Oh, guys?
It's not homosexuality, not drugs...
You're not gay? Right, guys?
No... no chance.
Well, then Hashim must
have some secret.
Some big secret
he's hiding from me.
See what's going on.
If you help us, you'll take
Dardan's place
and you'll receive 10 million euros
in a Swiss bank.
And if I don't help?
Then there will be
three funerals in Ulcinj.
And three coffins decorated
with Montenegrin ornaments.
Fuck, it took forever.
And you haven't moved, damn it!
You haven't changed at all,
a little here, but you're fine.
No wonder you fuck them all,
damn your mother!
Hey, I'm going to see
what's going on.
If I don't come back in half an hour,
disappear!
I'll call you when to come
and pick me up.
Come on!
Go!
Go, come on!
- What's happening, damn it?
Go!
Go quickly!
- Here, I'm going.
Go, go, brother, go!
Metya! Metya!
What happened with the knocking?
Her husband came home.
If you fuck married women,
they'll catch you someday, my friend.
You know what they say? "You can't
shake without getting slapped"!
Come on, hit one to calm down.
Oh damn, why did he close it?
Do you want?
Hey! Turn, turn!
Turn, turn that way!
Turn that way, come on! That way!
Relax, now I'll...
- Turn that way, damn it!
Turn!
Go, gas, gas!
Go quickly, brother!
Go, Ivan!
Uki-Tuki.
Oh, man...
Now you have to say
Ivek-Pimpek.
Ivan.
Uki-Tuki!
Oh, man...
Now you have to say Ivek-Pimpek.
Ivan.
You know what they say? "You can't
shake without getting slapped"!
Everyone stood and watched,
the whole high school.
And only you jumped to defend me.
You saved my life, Uki!
Translated by AcePhil